{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"9.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":8046,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":98,"width":1136,"height":640,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index_scorm.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Image_120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_120","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_147","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_147","title":"Começar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si611643","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Começar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si611663","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Começar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_118","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_118","title":"Teste de Nível ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5188","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_120","SmartShape_147","si611643","si611663","Text_Caption_118"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":135},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5188"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_149","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_149","title":"IR ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si619819","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"IR ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si619839","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"IR ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_119","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_119","title":"Section A1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_186","title":"Esta parte do teste tem 11 perguntas. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_187","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_187","title":"Você precisa de pelo menos 60% para passar para a próxima parte. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_188","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_188","title":"Você deve responder a cada pergunta e não pode voltar depois de enviar suas respostas. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_189","title":"Boa sorte!  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_124","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_124","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_125","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_125","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_190","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_190","title":"Olá ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_191","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_191","title":"Olá ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_126","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_126","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide201946","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_149","si619819","si619839","Text_Caption_119","SmartShape_186","SmartShape_187","SmartShape_188","SmartShape_189","Image_124","Image_125","SmartShape_190","SmartShape_191","Image_126"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":615},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide201946"}}},{"id":"si203919","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide203909q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si203953","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A: _________ your name? B: My name is Milena. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si203946","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Question 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si203968","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si203972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Where’s ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si203968_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Where’s\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si203979","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si203983","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"What’s ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si203979_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"What’s\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":9}}}},{"id":"si206203","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si206207","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"How’s ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si206203_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"How’s\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si206218","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si206222","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Which’s ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si206218_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Which’s\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si206233","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si206237","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"What ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si206233_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"What\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si204062","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide203909q0","for":"Slide203909q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si206548","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide203909q0","for":"Slide203909q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si228487","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide203909q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide203909","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si203919","si203953","si203946","si203972","si203983","si206207","si206222","si206237","si204062","si206548","si228487"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide203909"},"question":{"interactionId":"203933","quizId":382,"title":"Question 1\r","text":"A: _________ your name?\rB: My name is Milena.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si673924","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide673923q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673757","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_6","title":"A: Are they Spanish? B: No, they _________. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673770","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_16","title":"Question 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673781","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_17","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673785","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_18","title":"Brazilian ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673781_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Brazilian\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si673792","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_19","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_20","title":"are ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673792_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4","roles":{"answer":{"title":"are\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si673803","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_21","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673807","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_22","title":"don’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673803_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6","roles":{"answer":{"title":"don’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si673814","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_23","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673818","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_24","title":"Spanish ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673814_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Spanish\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si673825","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_25","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673829","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_26","title":"aren’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673825_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"10","roles":{"answer":{"title":"aren’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si673868","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_1","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide673923q1","for":"Slide673923q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673882","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_2","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide673923q1","for":"Slide673923q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673913","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_1","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide673923q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide673923","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si673924","si673757","si673770","si673785","si673796","si673807","si673818","si673829","si673868","si673882","si673913"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide673923"},"question":{"interactionId":"673743","quizId":382,"title":"Question 2\r","text":"A: Are they Spanish?\rB: No, they _________.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si674142","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide674141q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673975","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_27","title":"Jerry ___________ live in New York -- he lives in New Jersey. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673988","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_28","title":"Question 3 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673999","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_29","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674003","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_30","title":"doesn’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si673999_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_11","roles":{"answer":{"title":"doesn’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si674010","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_31","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674014","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_32","title":"isn’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674010_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_12","roles":{"answer":{"title":"isn’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si674021","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_33","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674025","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_34","title":"don’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674021_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_13","roles":{"answer":{"title":"don’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si674032","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_35","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674036","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_36","title":"not ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674032_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_14","roles":{"answer":{"title":"not\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si674043","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_37","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674047","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_38","title":"aren’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674043_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"10_15","roles":{"answer":{"title":"aren’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si674086","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_3","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide674141q2","for":"Slide674141q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674100","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide674141q2","for":"Slide674141q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674131","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide674141q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide674141","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si674142","si673975","si673988","si674003","si674014","si674025","si674036","si674047","si674086","si674100","si674131"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide674141"},"question":{"interactionId":"673961","quizId":382,"title":"Question 3\r","text":"Jerry ___________ live in New York -- he lives in New Jersey.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si674360","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide674359q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674193","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_39","title":"I’m sorry, but you _________ park here. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674206","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_40","title":"Question 4 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674217","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_41","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674221","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_42","title":"don’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674217_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_16","roles":{"answer":{"title":"don’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si674228","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_43","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674232","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_44","title":"aren’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674228_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_17","roles":{"answer":{"title":"aren’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si674239","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_45","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674243","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_46","title":"are ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674239_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_18","roles":{"answer":{"title":"are\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si674250","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_47","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674254","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_48","title":"can’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674250_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_19","roles":{"answer":{"title":"can’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si674261","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_49","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674265","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_50","title":"not ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674261_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"10_20","roles":{"answer":{"title":"not\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si674304","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_5","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide674359q3","for":"Slide674359q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674318","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_6","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide674359q3","for":"Slide674359q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_3","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide674359q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide674359","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si674360","si674193","si674206","si674221","si674232","si674243","si674254","si674265","si674304","si674318","si674349"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide674359"},"question":{"interactionId":"674179","quizId":382,"title":"Question 4\r","text":"I’m sorry, but you _________ park here.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si674578","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide674577q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674411","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_51","title":"What are you ________ to do tomorrow? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674424","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_52","title":"Question 5 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_53","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674439","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_54","title":"go ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674435_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_21","roles":{"answer":{"title":"go\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si674446","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_55","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674450","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_56","title":"going ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674446_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_22","roles":{"answer":{"title":"going\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si674457","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_57","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674461","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_58","title":"went ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674457_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_23","roles":{"answer":{"title":"went\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si674468","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_59","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674472","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_60","title":"doing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674468_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_24","roles":{"answer":{"title":"doing\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si674479","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_61","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674483","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_62","title":"will ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674479_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"10_25","roles":{"answer":{"title":"will\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si674522","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_7","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide674577q4","for":"Slide674577q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674536","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_8","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide674577q4","for":"Slide674577q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si674567","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_4","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide674577q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide674577","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si674578","si674411","si674424","si674439","si674450","si674461","si674472","si674483","si674522","si674536","si674567"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide674577"},"question":{"interactionId":"674397","quizId":382,"title":"Question 5\r","text":"What are you ________ to do tomorrow?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si680563","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide680562q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680379","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_64","title":"There _________ any people here at the moment. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680400","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_65","title":"Question 6 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680411","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_66","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680415","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_67","title":"is ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680411_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_26","roles":{"answer":{"title":"is\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si680422","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_68","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680426","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_69","title":"are ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680422_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_27","roles":{"answer":{"title":"are\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si680433","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_70","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680437","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_72","title":"aren’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680433_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_28","roles":{"answer":{"title":"aren’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si680444","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_73","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680448","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_74","title":"not ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680444_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_29","roles":{"answer":{"title":"not\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si680455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_75","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_76","title":"don’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680455_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"10_30","roles":{"answer":{"title":"don’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si680507","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide680562q5","for":"Slide680562q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680521","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_10","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide680562q5","for":"Slide680562q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680552","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_5","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide680562q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide680562","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si680563","si680379","si680400","si680415","si680426","si680437","si680448","si680459","si680507","si680521","si680552"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide680562"},"question":{"interactionId":"680326","quizId":382,"title":"Question 6\r","text":"There _________ any people here at the moment.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si681111","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide681110q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680927","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_78","title":"A: Do you know Rachel? B: Yes, I met _______ yesterday. She’s nice. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680948","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_79","title":"Question 7 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680968","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_88","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680972","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_89","title":"her ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680968_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_36","roles":{"answer":{"title":"her\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si680979","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_90","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680983","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_91","title":"hers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680979_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_37","roles":{"answer":{"title":"hers\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si680990","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_93","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680994","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_94","title":"him ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si680990_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_38","roles":{"answer":{"title":"him\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si681001","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_95","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681005","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_99","title":"she ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681001_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_39","roles":{"answer":{"title":"she\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si681012","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_100","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681016","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_101","title":"she’s ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681012_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"10_40","roles":{"answer":{"title":"she’s\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si681055","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_12","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide681110q6","for":"Slide681110q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681069","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_13","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide681110q6","for":"Slide681110q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681100","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_7","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide681110q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide681110","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si681111","si680927","si680948","si680972","si680983","si680994","si681005","si681016","si681055","si681069","si681100"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide681110"},"question":{"interactionId":"680874","quizId":382,"title":"Question 7\r","text":"A: Do you know Rachel?\rB: Yes, I met _______ yesterday. She’s nice.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si681385","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide681384q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_80","title":"A: Are you going to travel alone? B: _________________. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681222","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_81","title":"Question 8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681242","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_102","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681246","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_108","title":"No, I am. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681242_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_41","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No, I am.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si681253","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_113","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681257","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_116","title":"Yes, I’m. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681253_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_42","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes, I’m.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si681264","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_117","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681268","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_130","title":"No, I not. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681264_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_43","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No, I not.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si681275","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_131","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681279","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_135","title":"No, I’m not. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681275_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_44","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No, I’m not.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si681286","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_136","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681290","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_137","title":"Yes, it is. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681286_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"10_45","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes, it is.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si681329","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_14","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide681384q7","for":"Slide681384q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681343","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_15","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide681384q7","for":"Slide681384q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681374","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_8","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide681384q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide681384","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si681385","si681201","si681222","si681246","si681257","si681268","si681279","si681290","si681329","si681343","si681374"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide681384"},"question":{"interactionId":"681148","quizId":382,"title":"Question 8\r","text":"A: Are you going to travel alone?\rB: _________________.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si681659","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide681658q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681475","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_82","title":"Where’s ____________ sister? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681496","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_83","title":"Question 9 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681516","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_138","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681520","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_139","title":"Sophies ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681516_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_46","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Sophies\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si681527","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_140","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681531","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_141","title":"Sophie’s ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681527_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_47","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Sophie’s\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si681538","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_142","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681542","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_143","title":"Sophie ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681538_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_48","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Sophie\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si681549","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_144","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681553","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_145","title":"Sophie is ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681549_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_49","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Sophie is\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si681560","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_146","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681564","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_147","title":"is Sophie ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681560_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"10_50","roles":{"answer":{"title":"is Sophie\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si681603","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_16","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide681658q8","for":"Slide681658q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681617","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_17","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide681658q8","for":"Slide681658q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681648","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide681658q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide681658","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si681659","si681475","si681496","si681520","si681531","si681542","si681553","si681564","si681603","si681617","si681648"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide681658"},"question":{"interactionId":"681422","quizId":382,"title":"Question 9\r","text":"Where’s ____________ sister?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si681933","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide681932q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681749","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_84","title":"I _______________ at eight o’clock. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681770","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_85","title":"Question 10 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681790","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_148","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681794","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_149","title":"start work usually ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681790_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_51","roles":{"answer":{"title":"start work usually\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si681801","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_150","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681805","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_151","title":"usually start work ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681801_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_52","roles":{"answer":{"title":"usually start work\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si681812","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_152","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681816","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_153","title":"start usually work ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681812_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_53","roles":{"answer":{"title":"start usually work\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si681823","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_154","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681827","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_155","title":"work usually start ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681823_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_54","roles":{"answer":{"title":"work usually start\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si681834","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_156","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681838","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_157","title":"work start usually ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681834_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"10_55","roles":{"answer":{"title":"work start usually\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si681877","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_18","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide681932q9","for":"Slide681932q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681891","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_19","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide681932q9","for":"Slide681932q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si681922","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_10","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide681932q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide681932","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si681933","si681749","si681770","si681794","si681805","si681816","si681827","si681838","si681877","si681891","si681922"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide681932"},"question":{"interactionId":"681696","quizId":382,"title":"Question 10\r","text":"I _______________ at eight o’clock.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si682207","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide682206q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si682023","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_86","title":"My sister ______________ in Rio de Janeiro. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si682044","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_87","title":"Question 11 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si682064","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_158","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si682068","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_159","title":"isn’t live ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si682064_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_56","roles":{"answer":{"title":"isn’t live\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si682075","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_160","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si682079","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_161","title":"doesn’t live ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si682075_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_57","roles":{"answer":{"title":"doesn’t live\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si682086","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_162","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si682090","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_163","title":"don’t live ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si682086_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_58","roles":{"answer":{"title":"don’t live\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si682097","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_164","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si682101","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_165","title":"live ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si682097_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_59","roles":{"answer":{"title":"live\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si682108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_166","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si682112","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_167","title":"not live ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si682108_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"10_60","roles":{"answer":{"title":"not live\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si682151","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_20","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide682206q10","for":"Slide682206q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si682165","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_21","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide682206q10","for":"Slide682206q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si682196","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_11","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide682206q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide682206","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si682207","si682023","si682044","si682068","si682079","si682090","si682101","si682112","si682151","si682165","si682196"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide682206"},"question":{"interactionId":"681970","quizId":382,"title":"Question 11\r","text":"My sister ______________ in Rio de Janeiro.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_33","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si226730","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si226742","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_120","title":"End of Section A1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide226702","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_33","si226730","si226742","Text_Caption_120"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide226702"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_192","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_192","title":"IR ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si686428","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"IR ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si686439","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"IR ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_168","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_168","title":"Section A2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_193","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_193","title":"Esta parte do teste tem 15 perguntas. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_194","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_194","title":"Você precisa de pelo menos 60% para passar para a próxima parte. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_195","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_195","title":"Você deve responder a cada pergunta e não pode voltar depois de enviar suas respostas. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_196","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_196","title":"Boa sorte!  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_197","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_197","title":"Good Job ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_198","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_198","title":"Thanks ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_130","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_130","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_131","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_131","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide686558","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_192","si686428","si686439","Text_Caption_168","SmartShape_193","SmartShape_194","SmartShape_195","SmartShape_196","SmartShape_197","SmartShape_198","Image_130","Image_131"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":618},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide686558"}}},{"id":"si687948","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide687947q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687764","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_124","title":"Where’s John? He _________ late.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687785","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_128","title":"Question 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687805","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_176","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687809","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_177","title":"does ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687805_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61","roles":{"answer":{"title":"does\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si687816","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_178","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687820","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_179","title":"is ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687816_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64","roles":{"answer":{"title":"is\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":9}}}},{"id":"si687827","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_180","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687831","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_181","title":"get ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687827_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66","roles":{"answer":{"title":"get\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si687838","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_182","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687842","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_183","title":"don’t get ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687838_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68","roles":{"answer":{"title":"don’t get\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si687849","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_184","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687853","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_185","title":"has ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687849_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70","roles":{"answer":{"title":"has\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si687892","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_22","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide687947q11","for":"Slide687947q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687906","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_23","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide687947q11","for":"Slide687947q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687937","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_12","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide687947q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide687947","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si687948","si687764","si687785","si687809","si687820","si687831","si687842","si687853","si687892","si687906","si687937"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide687947"},"question":{"interactionId":"687711","quizId":382,"title":"Question 1\r","text":"Where’s John? He _________ late. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si688222","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide688221q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688038","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_186","title":"She’s in my class. _________ name is Melissa. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688059","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_187","title":"Question 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688079","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_188","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688083","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_189","title":"Her ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688079_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_71","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Her\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si688090","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_190","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688094","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_191","title":"She’s ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688090_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_72","roles":{"answer":{"title":"She’s\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si688101","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_192","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688105","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_193","title":"She ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688101_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_73","roles":{"answer":{"title":"She\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si688112","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_194","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688116","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_195","title":"Hers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688112_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_74","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Hers\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si688123","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_196","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688127","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_197","title":"His ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688123_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_75","roles":{"answer":{"title":"His\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si688166","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_24","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide688221q12","for":"Slide688221q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688180","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_25","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide688221q12","for":"Slide688221q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688211","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_13","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide688221q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide688221","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si688222","si688038","si688059","si688083","si688094","si688105","si688116","si688127","si688166","si688180","si688211"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide688221"},"question":{"interactionId":"687985","quizId":382,"title":"Question 2\r","text":"She’s in my class. _________ name is Melissa.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si688496","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide688495q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688312","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_198","title":"A: I have a difficult test tomorrow. B: _______ worry. You’ll get a good grade.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688333","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_199","title":"Question 3 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688353","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_200","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688357","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_201","title":"No ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688353_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_76","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si688364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_202","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688368","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_203","title":"Isn’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688364_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_77","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Isn’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si688375","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_204","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688379","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_205","title":"Can’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688375_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_78","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Can’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si688386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_206","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688390","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_207","title":"Don’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688386_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_79","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Don’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si688397","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_208","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688401","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_209","title":"Have ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688397_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_80","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Have\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si688440","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_26","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide688495q13","for":"Slide688495q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688454","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_27","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide688495q13","for":"Slide688495q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688485","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_14","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide688495q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide688495","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si688496","si688312","si688333","si688357","si688368","si688379","si688390","si688401","si688440","si688454","si688485"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide688495"},"question":{"interactionId":"688259","quizId":382,"title":"Question 3\r","text":"A: I have a difficult test tomorrow.\rB: _______ worry. You’ll get a good grade. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si688770","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide688769q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688586","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_210","title":"_____________ another language? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688607","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_211","title":"Question 4 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688627","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_212","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688631","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_213","title":"You speak ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688627_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_81","roles":{"answer":{"title":"You speak\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si688638","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_214","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688642","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_215","title":"Are you speak ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688638_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_82","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Are you speak\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si688649","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_216","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688653","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_217","title":"Do you speak ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688649_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_83","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Do you speak\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si688660","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_218","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688664","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_219","title":"Speak you ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688660_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_84","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Speak you\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si688671","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_220","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688675","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_221","title":"Is you speak ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688671_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_85","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Is you speak\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si688714","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_28","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide688769q14","for":"Slide688769q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688728","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_29","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide688769q14","for":"Slide688769q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688759","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_15","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide688769q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide688769","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si688770","si688586","si688607","si688631","si688642","si688653","si688664","si688675","si688714","si688728","si688759"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide688769"},"question":{"interactionId":"688533","quizId":382,"title":"Question 4\r","text":"_____________ another language?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si689044","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide689043q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688860","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_222","title":"How old ____________? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688881","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_223","title":"Question 5 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688901","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_224","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688905","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_225","title":"do you have ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688901_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_86","roles":{"answer":{"title":"do you have\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si688912","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_226","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688916","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_227","title":"are you ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688912_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_87","roles":{"answer":{"title":"are you\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si688923","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_228","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688927","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_229","title":"are you having ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688923_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_88","roles":{"answer":{"title":"are you having\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si688934","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_230","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688938","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_231","title":"you are ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688934_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_89","roles":{"answer":{"title":"you are\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si688945","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_232","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688949","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_233","title":"you have ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si688945_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_90","roles":{"answer":{"title":"you have\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si688988","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_30","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide689043q15","for":"Slide689043q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689002","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_31","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide689043q15","for":"Slide689043q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689033","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_16","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide689043q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide689043","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si689044","si688860","si688881","si688905","si688916","si688927","si688938","si688949","si688988","si689002","si689033"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide689043"},"question":{"interactionId":"688807","quizId":382,"title":"Question 5\r","text":"How old ____________?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si689318","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide689317q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689134","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_234","title":"__________ for my class. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689155","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_235","title":"Question 6 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689175","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_236","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689179","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_237","title":"Never I am late ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689175_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_91","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Never I am late\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si689186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_238","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689190","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_239","title":"Late never am I ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689186_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_92","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Late never am I\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si689197","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_240","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_241","title":"I am late never ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689197_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_93","roles":{"answer":{"title":"I am late never\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si689208","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_242","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689212","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_243","title":"I never late ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689208_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_94","roles":{"answer":{"title":"I never late\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si689219","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_244","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689223","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_245","title":"I am never late ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689219_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_95","roles":{"answer":{"title":"I am never late\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si689262","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_32","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide689317q16","for":"Slide689317q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689276","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_33","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide689317q16","for":"Slide689317q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689307","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_17","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide689317q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide689317","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si689318","si689134","si689155","si689179","si689190","si689201","si689212","si689223","si689262","si689276","si689307"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide689317"},"question":{"interactionId":"689081","quizId":382,"title":"Question 6\r","text":"__________ for my class.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si689592","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide689591q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689408","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_246","title":"A: What __________? B: Nothing special, just watching TV. Why? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_247","title":"Question 7 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689449","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_248","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689453","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_249","title":"are you doing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689449_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_96","roles":{"answer":{"title":"are you doing\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si689460","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_250","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689464","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_251","title":"you do ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689460_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_97","roles":{"answer":{"title":"you do\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si689471","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_252","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689475","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_253","title":"do you doing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689471_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_98","roles":{"answer":{"title":"do you doing\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si689482","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_254","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689486","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_255","title":"are you do ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689482_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_99","roles":{"answer":{"title":"are you do\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si689493","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_256","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689497","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_257","title":"you doing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689493_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_100","roles":{"answer":{"title":"you doing\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si689536","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_34","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide689591q17","for":"Slide689591q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689550","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_35","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide689591q17","for":"Slide689591q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689581","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_18","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide689591q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide689591","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si689592","si689408","si689429","si689453","si689464","si689475","si689486","si689497","si689536","si689550","si689581"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide689591"},"question":{"interactionId":"689355","quizId":382,"title":"Question 7\r","text":"A: What __________?\rB: Nothing special, just watching TV. Why?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si689866","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide689865q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689682","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_258","title":"This is our teacher, Professor Kent. We like __________. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689703","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_259","title":"Question 8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689723","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_260","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689727","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_261","title":"he ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689723_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_101","roles":{"answer":{"title":"he\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si689734","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_262","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_263","title":"his ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689734_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_102","roles":{"answer":{"title":"his\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si689745","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_264","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689749","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_265","title":"she ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689745_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_103","roles":{"answer":{"title":"she\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si689756","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_266","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689760","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_267","title":"hers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689756_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_104","roles":{"answer":{"title":"hers\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si689767","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_268","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689771","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_269","title":"him ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689767_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_105","roles":{"answer":{"title":"him\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si689810","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_37","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide689865q18","for":"Slide689865q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689824","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_38","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide689865q18","for":"Slide689865q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689855","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_19","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide689865q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide689865","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si689866","si689682","si689703","si689727","si689738","si689749","si689760","si689771","si689810","si689824","si689855"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide689865"},"question":{"interactionId":"689629","quizId":382,"title":"Question 8\r","text":"This is our teacher, Professor Kent. We like __________.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si690140","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide690139q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689956","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_270","title":"__________ it hot yesterday? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689977","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_271","title":"Question 9 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689997","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_272","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690001","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_273","title":"Did ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si689997_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_106","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Did\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si690008","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_274","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690012","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_275","title":"Is ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690008_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_107","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Is\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si690019","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_276","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690023","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_277","title":"Was ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690019_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_108","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Was\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si690030","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_278","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690034","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_279","title":"Does ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690030_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_109","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Does\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si690041","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_280","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690045","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_281","title":"Will ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690041_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_110","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Will\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si690084","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_39","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide690139q19","for":"Slide690139q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690098","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_40","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide690139q19","for":"Slide690139q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690129","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_20","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide690139q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide690139","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si690140","si689956","si689977","si690001","si690012","si690023","si690034","si690045","si690084","si690098","si690129"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide690139"},"question":{"interactionId":"689903","quizId":382,"title":"Question 9\r","text":"__________ it hot yesterday?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si690848","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide690847q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690664","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_306","title":"How _________ home? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690685","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_307","title":"Question 10 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690705","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_308","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690709","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_309","title":"were you get ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690705_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_124","roles":{"answer":{"title":"were you get\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si690716","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_310","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690720","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_311","title":"did you get ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690716_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_125","roles":{"answer":{"title":"did you get\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si690727","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_312","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690731","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_313","title":"did you got ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690727_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_126","roles":{"answer":{"title":"did you got\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si690738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_314","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690742","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_315","title":"you got  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690738_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_127","roles":{"answer":{"title":"you got \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si690749","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_316","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690753","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_317","title":"got you ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690749_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_128","roles":{"answer":{"title":"got you\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si690792","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_45","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide690847q20","for":"Slide690847q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690806","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_46","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide690847q20","for":"Slide690847q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690837","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_23","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide690847q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide690847","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si690848","si690664","si690685","si690709","si690720","si690731","si690742","si690753","si690792","si690806","si690837"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide690847"},"question":{"interactionId":"690611","quizId":382,"title":"Question 10\r","text":"How _________ home?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si691122","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide691121q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690938","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_318","title":"____________ in the hotel? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690959","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_319","title":"Question 11 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690979","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_320","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690983","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_321","title":"How many guests was ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690979_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_129","roles":{"answer":{"title":"How many guests was\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si690990","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_322","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690994","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_323","title":"How much guests were there ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si690990_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_130","roles":{"answer":{"title":"How much guests were there\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si691001","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_324","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691005","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_325","title":"How many were ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691001_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_131","roles":{"answer":{"title":"How many were\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si691012","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_326","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691016","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"How much was ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691012_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_132","roles":{"answer":{"title":"How much was\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si691023","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_328","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691027","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"How many guests were there ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691023_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_133","roles":{"answer":{"title":"How many guests were there\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si691066","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_47","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide691121q21","for":"Slide691121q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691080","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_48","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide691121q21","for":"Slide691121q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691111","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_24","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide691121q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide691121","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si691122","si690938","si690959","si690983","si690994","si691005","si691016","si691027","si691066","si691080","si691111"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide691121"},"question":{"interactionId":"690885","quizId":382,"title":"Question 11\r","text":"____________ in the hotel?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si691396","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide691395q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691212","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_330","title":"__________ cookies did you eat? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691233","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"Question 12 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691253","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691257","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"How much ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691253_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_134","roles":{"answer":{"title":"How much\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si691264","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691268","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"What numbers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691264_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_135","roles":{"answer":{"title":"What numbers\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si691275","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691279","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","title":"Where ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691275_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_136","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Where\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si691286","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691290","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_339","title":"How many ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691286_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_137","roles":{"answer":{"title":"How many\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si691297","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_340","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691301","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_341","title":"When ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691297_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_138","roles":{"answer":{"title":"When\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si691340","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_49","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide691395q22","for":"Slide691395q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691354","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_50","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide691395q22","for":"Slide691395q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691385","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_26","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide691395q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide691395","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si691396","si691212","si691233","si691257","si691268","si691279","si691290","si691301","si691340","si691354","si691385"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide691395"},"question":{"interactionId":"691159","quizId":382,"title":"Question 12\r","text":"__________ cookies did you eat?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si691670","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide691669q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691486","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_342","title":"CBA is __________ English school we have ever worked at. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691507","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_343","title":"Question 13 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691527","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_344","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691531","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_345","title":"the best ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691527_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_139","roles":{"answer":{"title":"the best\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si691538","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_346","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691542","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_347","title":"the good ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691538_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_140","roles":{"answer":{"title":"the good\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si691549","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_348","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691553","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_349","title":"the goodest ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691549_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_141","roles":{"answer":{"title":"the goodest\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si691560","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_350","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691564","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_351","title":"better ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691560_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_142","roles":{"answer":{"title":"better\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si691571","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_352","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691575","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_353","title":"best ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691571_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_143","roles":{"answer":{"title":"best\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si691614","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_51","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide691669q23","for":"Slide691669q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691628","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_52","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide691669q23","for":"Slide691669q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691659","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_27","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide691669q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide691669","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si691670","si691486","si691507","si691531","si691542","si691553","si691564","si691575","si691614","si691628","si691659"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide691669"},"question":{"interactionId":"691433","quizId":382,"title":"Question 13\r","text":"CBA is __________ English school we have ever worked at.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si691944","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide691943q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691760","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_354","title":"A: ___________ abroad? B: No, I haven’t. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691781","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_355","title":"Question 15 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691801","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_356","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691805","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_357","title":"You ever travel ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691801_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_144","roles":{"answer":{"title":"You ever travel\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si691812","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_358","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691816","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_359","title":"Have you ever traveled ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691812_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_145","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Have you ever traveled\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si691823","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_360","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691827","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_361","title":"Have you travel ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691823_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_146","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Have you travel\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si691834","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_362","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691838","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_363","title":"Are you ever traveled ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691834_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_147","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Are you ever traveled\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si691845","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_364","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691849","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_365","title":"Are you traveling ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691845_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_148","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Are you traveling\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si691888","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_53","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide691943q24","for":"Slide691943q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691902","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_54","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide691943q24","for":"Slide691943q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si691933","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_28","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide691943q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide691943","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si691944","si691760","si691781","si691805","si691816","si691827","si691838","si691849","si691888","si691902","si691933"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide691943"},"question":{"interactionId":"691707","quizId":382,"title":"Question 15\r","text":"A: ___________ abroad?\rB: No, I haven’t.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_220","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_220","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687286","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687297","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_172","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_172","title":"End of Section A2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide687342","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_220","si687286","si687297","Text_Caption_172"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide687342"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_169","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_169","title":"Section A2+/B1- ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_200","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_200","title":"Esta parte do teste tem 18 perguntas. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_201","title":"Você precisa de pelo menos 60% para passar para a próxima parte. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_202","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_202","title":"Você deve responder a cada pergunta e não pode voltar depois de enviar suas respostas. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_203","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_203","title":"Boa sorte!  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_204","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_204","title":"Keep It Up! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_205","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_205","title":"OK! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_132","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_133","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_133","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_224","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_224","title":"IR ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si721282","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"IR ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si721302","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"IR ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide686800","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_169","SmartShape_200","SmartShape_201","SmartShape_202","SmartShape_203","SmartShape_204","SmartShape_205","Image_132","Image_133","SmartShape_224","si721282","si721302"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":630},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide686800"}}},{"id":"si692218","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide692217q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692034","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_366","title":"The gym ___________ on Wednesdays. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692055","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_367","title":"Question 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692075","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_368","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692079","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_369","title":"isn’t cleans ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692075_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_149","roles":{"answer":{"title":"isn’t cleans\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si692086","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_370","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692090","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_371","title":"cleaned ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692086_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_150","roles":{"answer":{"title":"cleaned\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si692097","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_372","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692101","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_373","title":"doesn’t clean ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692097_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_151","roles":{"answer":{"title":"doesn’t clean\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si692108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_374","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692112","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_375","title":"cleans ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692108_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_152","roles":{"answer":{"title":"cleans\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si692119","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_376","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692123","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_377","title":"isn’t cleaned ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692119_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_153","roles":{"answer":{"title":"isn’t cleaned\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si692162","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_55","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide692217q25","for":"Slide692217q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692176","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_56","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide692217q25","for":"Slide692217q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692207","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_29","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide692217q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide692217","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si692218","si692034","si692055","si692079","si692090","si692101","si692112","si692123","si692162","si692176","si692207"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide692217"},"question":{"interactionId":"691981","quizId":382,"title":"Question 1\r","text":"The gym ___________ on Wednesdays.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si692492","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide692491q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692308","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_378","title":"When we arrived, they _______ already ______ -- the house was empty.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692329","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_379","title":"Question 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_380","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692353","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_381","title":"have -- left ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692349_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_154","roles":{"answer":{"title":"have -- left\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si692360","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_382","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_383","title":"had -- left ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692360_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_155","roles":{"answer":{"title":"had -- left\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si692371","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_384","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692375","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_385","title":"had -- been leaving ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692371_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_156","roles":{"answer":{"title":"had -- been leaving\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si692382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_386","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_387","title":"have -- been leaving ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692382_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_157","roles":{"answer":{"title":"have -- been leaving\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si692393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_388","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692397","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_389","title":"were -- left ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692393_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_158","roles":{"answer":{"title":"were -- left\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si692436","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_57","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide692491q26","for":"Slide692491q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692450","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_58","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide692491q26","for":"Slide692491q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692481","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_30","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide692491q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide692491","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si692492","si692308","si692329","si692353","si692364","si692375","si692386","si692397","si692436","si692450","si692481"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide692491"},"question":{"interactionId":"692255","quizId":382,"title":"Question 2\r","text":"When we arrived, they _______ already ______ -- the house was empty. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si693040","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide693039q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692856","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_402","title":"I don’t think it ________ this week. It’s too warm. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692877","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_403","title":"Question 3 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692897","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_404","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692901","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_405","title":"will snow ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692897_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_164","roles":{"answer":{"title":"will snow\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si692908","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_406","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692912","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_407","title":"will to snow ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692908_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_165","roles":{"answer":{"title":"will to snow\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si692919","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_408","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692923","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_409","title":"is snowing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692919_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_166","roles":{"answer":{"title":"is snowing\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si692930","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_410","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692934","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_411","title":"snow ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692930_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_167","roles":{"answer":{"title":"snow\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si692941","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_412","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692945","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_413","title":"might to snow ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692941_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_168","roles":{"answer":{"title":"might to snow\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si692984","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_61","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide693039q27","for":"Slide693039q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si692998","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_62","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide693039q27","for":"Slide693039q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693029","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_32","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide693039q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide693039","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si693040","si692856","si692877","si692901","si692912","si692923","si692934","si692945","si692984","si692998","si693029"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide693039"},"question":{"interactionId":"692803","quizId":382,"title":"Question 3\r","text":"I don’t think it ________ this week. It’s too warm.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si693314","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide693313q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693130","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_414","title":"We left the movie theater because we ________ the movie before.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693151","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_415","title":"Question 4 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693171","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_416","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693175","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_417","title":"saw ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693171_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_169","roles":{"answer":{"title":"saw\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si693182","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_418","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_419","title":"have seen ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693182_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_170","roles":{"answer":{"title":"have seen\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si693193","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_420","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693197","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_421","title":"had seen ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693193_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_171","roles":{"answer":{"title":"had seen\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si693204","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_422","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693208","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_423","title":"have been seeing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693204_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_172","roles":{"answer":{"title":"have been seeing\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si693215","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_424","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693219","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_425","title":"had been seeing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693215_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_173","roles":{"answer":{"title":"had been seeing\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si693258","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_63","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide693313q28","for":"Slide693313q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693272","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_64","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide693313q28","for":"Slide693313q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693303","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_34","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide693313q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide693313","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si693314","si693130","si693151","si693175","si693186","si693197","si693208","si693219","si693258","si693272","si693303"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide693313"},"question":{"interactionId":"693077","quizId":382,"title":"Question 4\r","text":"We left the movie theater because we ________ the movie before. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si693588","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide693587q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693404","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_426","title":"_________ bread did you eat? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693425","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_427","title":"Question 5 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693445","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_428","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693449","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_429","title":"How much ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693445_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_174","roles":{"answer":{"title":"How much\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si693456","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_430","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693460","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_431","title":"How many ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693456_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_175","roles":{"answer":{"title":"How many\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si693467","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_432","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693471","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_433","title":"Many ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693467_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_176","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Many\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si693478","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_434","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693482","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_435","title":"Much ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693478_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_177","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Much\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si693489","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_436","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693493","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_437","title":"How ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693489_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_178","roles":{"answer":{"title":"How\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si693532","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_65","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide693587q29","for":"Slide693587q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693546","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_66","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide693587q29","for":"Slide693587q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693577","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_35","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide693587q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide693587","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si693588","si693404","si693425","si693449","si693460","si693471","si693482","si693493","si693532","si693546","si693577"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide693587"},"question":{"interactionId":"693351","quizId":382,"title":"Question 5\r","text":"_________ bread did you eat?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si693862","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide693861q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693678","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_438","title":"I went to Rome _______ learn Italian. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693699","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_439","title":"Question 6 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693719","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_440","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693723","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_441","title":"by ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693719_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_179","roles":{"answer":{"title":"by\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si693730","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_442","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693734","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_443","title":"for ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693730_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_180","roles":{"answer":{"title":"for\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si693741","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_444","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693745","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_445","title":"because I want ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693741_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_181","roles":{"answer":{"title":"because I want\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si693752","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_446","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693756","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_447","title":"to ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693752_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_182","roles":{"answer":{"title":"to\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si693763","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_448","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693767","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_449","title":"so ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693763_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_183","roles":{"answer":{"title":"so\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si693806","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_67","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide693861q30","for":"Slide693861q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693820","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_68","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide693861q30","for":"Slide693861q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693851","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_36","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide693861q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide693861","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si693862","si693678","si693699","si693723","si693734","si693745","si693756","si693767","si693806","si693820","si693851"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide693861"},"question":{"interactionId":"693625","quizId":382,"title":"Question 6\r","text":"I went to Rome _______ learn Italian.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si694136","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide694135q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693952","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_450","title":"A: Have you heard the news?  B: No, not _______. What happened? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693973","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_451","title":"Question 7 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693993","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_452","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693997","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_453","title":"yet  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si693993_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_184","roles":{"answer":{"title":"yet \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si694004","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_454","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694008","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_455","title":"already ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694004_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_185","roles":{"answer":{"title":"already\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si694015","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_456","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694019","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_457","title":"just  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694015_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_186","roles":{"answer":{"title":"just \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si694026","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_458","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694030","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_459","title":"now ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694026_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_187","roles":{"answer":{"title":"now\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si694037","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_460","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694041","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_461","title":"at the moment ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694037_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_188","roles":{"answer":{"title":"at the moment\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si694080","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_69","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide694135q31","for":"Slide694135q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694094","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_70","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide694135q31","for":"Slide694135q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694125","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_37","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide694135q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide694135","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si694136","si693952","si693973","si693997","si694008","si694019","si694030","si694041","si694080","si694094","si694125"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide694135"},"question":{"interactionId":"693899","quizId":382,"title":"Question 7\r","text":"A: Have you heard the news? \rB: No, not _______. What happened?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si694410","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide694409q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694226","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_462","title":"This bike’s _________ mine. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694247","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_463","title":"Question 8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694267","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_464","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694271","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_465","title":"much expensive than ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694267_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_189","roles":{"answer":{"title":"much expensive than\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si694278","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_466","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694282","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_467","title":"more expensive than ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694278_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_190","roles":{"answer":{"title":"more expensive than\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si694289","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_468","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694293","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_469","title":"expensiver than ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694289_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_191","roles":{"answer":{"title":"expensiver than\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si694300","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_470","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694304","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_471","title":"the most expensive ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694300_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_192","roles":{"answer":{"title":"the most expensive\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si694311","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_472","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694315","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_473","title":"the more expensive ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694311_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_193","roles":{"answer":{"title":"the more expensive\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si694354","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_71","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide694409q32","for":"Slide694409q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694368","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_72","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide694409q32","for":"Slide694409q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694399","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_38","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide694409q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide694409","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si694410","si694226","si694247","si694271","si694282","si694293","si694304","si694315","si694354","si694368","si694399"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide694409"},"question":{"interactionId":"694173","quizId":382,"title":"Question 8\r","text":"This bike’s _________ mine.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si694684","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide694683q33"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694500","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_474","title":"They _________ to the beach tomorrow -- if the weather is hot.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694521","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_475","title":"Question 9 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694541","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_476","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694545","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_477","title":"must go ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694541_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_194","roles":{"answer":{"title":"must go\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si694552","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_478","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694556","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_479","title":"might to go ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694552_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_195","roles":{"answer":{"title":"might to go\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si694563","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_480","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694567","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_481","title":"may to go ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694563_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_196","roles":{"answer":{"title":"may to go\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si694574","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_482","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694578","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_483","title":"might go ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694574_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_197","roles":{"answer":{"title":"might go\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si694585","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_484","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694589","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_485","title":"must to go ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694585_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_198","roles":{"answer":{"title":"must to go\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si694628","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_73","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide694683q33","for":"Slide694683q33"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694642","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_74","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide694683q33","for":"Slide694683q33"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694673","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_39","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide694683q33"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide694683","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si694684","si694500","si694521","si694545","si694556","si694567","si694578","si694589","si694628","si694642","si694673"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide694683"},"question":{"interactionId":"694447","quizId":382,"title":"Question 9\r","text":"They _________ to the beach tomorrow -- if the weather is hot. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si694958","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide694957q34"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694774","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_486","title":"She ________ us she was busy this weekend.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694795","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_487","title":"Question 10 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694815","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_488","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694819","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_489","title":"said ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694815_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_199","roles":{"answer":{"title":"said\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si694826","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_490","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694830","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_491","title":"telled ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694826_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_200","roles":{"answer":{"title":"telled\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si694837","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_492","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694841","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_493","title":"told ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694837_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_201","roles":{"answer":{"title":"told\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si694848","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_494","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694852","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_495","title":"asked ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694848_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_202","roles":{"answer":{"title":"asked\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si694859","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_496","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694863","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_497","title":"have told ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694859_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_203","roles":{"answer":{"title":"have told\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si694902","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_75","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide694957q34","for":"Slide694957q34"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694916","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_76","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide694957q34","for":"Slide694957q34"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si694947","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_40","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide694957q34"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide694957","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si694958","si694774","si694795","si694819","si694830","si694841","si694852","si694863","si694902","si694916","si694947"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide694957"},"question":{"interactionId":"694721","quizId":382,"title":"Question 10\r","text":"She ________ us she was busy this weekend. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si695232","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide695231q35"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695048","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_498","title":"I don’t want to go to the conference but I have to. If I __________, I ___________ to that conference. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695069","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_499","title":"Question 11 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695089","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_500","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695093","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_501","title":"have to -- wouldn’t have gone ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695089_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_204","roles":{"answer":{"title":"have to -- wouldn’t have gone\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si695100","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_502","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695104","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_503","title":"hadn’t to -- wouldn’t go ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695100_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_205","roles":{"answer":{"title":"hadn’t to -- wouldn’t go\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si695111","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_504","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695115","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_505","title":"don’t have to -- won’t go ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695111_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_206","roles":{"answer":{"title":"don’t have to -- won’t go\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si695122","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_506","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695126","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_507","title":"didn’t have to -- wouldn’t go ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695122_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_207","roles":{"answer":{"title":"didn’t have to -- wouldn’t go\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si695133","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_508","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695137","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_509","title":"didn’t have -- wouldn’t have gone ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695133_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_208","roles":{"answer":{"title":"didn’t have -- wouldn’t have gone\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si695176","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_77","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide695231q35","for":"Slide695231q35"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695190","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_78","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide695231q35","for":"Slide695231q35"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695221","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_41","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide695231q35"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide695231","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si695232","si695048","si695069","si695093","si695104","si695115","si695126","si695137","si695176","si695190","si695221"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide695231"},"question":{"interactionId":"694995","quizId":382,"title":"Question 11\r","text":"I don’t want to go to the conference but I have to. If I __________, I ___________ to that conference.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si695780","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide695779q36"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695596","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_511","title":"My brother is my aunt’s ________. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695617","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_512","title":"Question 12 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695637","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_521","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695641","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_522","title":"niece ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695637_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_214","roles":{"answer":{"title":"niece\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si695648","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_523","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695652","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_524","title":"nephew ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695648_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_215","roles":{"answer":{"title":"nephew\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si695659","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_525","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695663","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_526","title":"grandson ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695659_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_216","roles":{"answer":{"title":"grandson\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si695670","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_527","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695674","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_528","title":"cousin ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695670_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_217","roles":{"answer":{"title":"cousin\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si695681","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_529","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695685","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_530","title":"fiancé ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695681_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_218","roles":{"answer":{"title":"fiancé\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si695724","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_80","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide695779q36","for":"Slide695779q36"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_81","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide695779q36","for":"Slide695779q36"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695769","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_43","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide695779q36"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide695779","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si695780","si695596","si695617","si695641","si695652","si695663","si695674","si695685","si695724","si695738","si695769"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide695779"},"question":{"interactionId":"695543","quizId":382,"title":"Question 12\r","text":"My brother is my aunt’s ________.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si696054","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide696053q37"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695870","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_513","title":"Is he looking _____ to the party? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695891","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_514","title":"Question 13 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695911","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_531","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695915","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_532","title":"after ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695911_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_219","roles":{"answer":{"title":"after\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si695922","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_533","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695926","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_534","title":"forward ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695922_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_220","roles":{"answer":{"title":"forward\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si695933","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_535","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695937","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_536","title":"for ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695933_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_221","roles":{"answer":{"title":"for\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si695944","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_537","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695948","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_538","title":"in ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695944_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_222","roles":{"answer":{"title":"in\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si695955","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_539","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695959","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_540","title":"by ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si695955_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_223","roles":{"answer":{"title":"by\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si695998","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_82","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide696053q37","for":"Slide696053q37"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696012","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_83","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide696053q37","for":"Slide696053q37"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696043","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_44","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide696053q37"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide696053","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si696054","si695870","si695891","si695915","si695926","si695937","si695948","si695959","si695998","si696012","si696043"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide696053"},"question":{"interactionId":"695817","quizId":382,"title":"Question 13\r","text":"Is he looking _____ to the party?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si696328","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide696327q38"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696144","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_515","title":"Enter our competition now! You could ______ a great prize! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696165","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_516","title":"Question 14 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_541","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_542","title":"do ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696185_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_224","roles":{"answer":{"title":"do\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si696196","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_543","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696200","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_544","title":"earn ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696196_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_225","roles":{"answer":{"title":"earn\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si696207","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_545","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696211","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_546","title":"make ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696207_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_226","roles":{"answer":{"title":"make\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si696218","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_547","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696222","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_548","title":"win ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696218_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_227","roles":{"answer":{"title":"win\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si696229","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_549","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696233","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_550","title":"have ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696229_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_228","roles":{"answer":{"title":"have\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si696272","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_84","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide696327q38","for":"Slide696327q38"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696286","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_85","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide696327q38","for":"Slide696327q38"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696317","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_45","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide696327q38"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide696327","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si696328","si696144","si696165","si696189","si696200","si696211","si696222","si696233","si696272","si696286","si696317"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide696327"},"question":{"interactionId":"696091","quizId":382,"title":"Question 14\r","text":"Enter our competition now! You could ______ a great prize!\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si696602","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide696601q39"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696418","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_517","title":"He _______ along really well with his sister.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696439","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_518","title":"Question 15 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_551","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696463","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_552","title":"does ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696459_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_229","roles":{"answer":{"title":"does\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si696470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_553","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696474","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_554","title":"goes ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696470_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_230","roles":{"answer":{"title":"goes\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si696481","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_555","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696485","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_556","title":"makes ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696481_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_231","roles":{"answer":{"title":"makes\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si696492","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_557","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696496","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_558","title":"gets ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696492_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_232","roles":{"answer":{"title":"gets\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si696503","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_559","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696507","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_560","title":"takes ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696503_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_233","roles":{"answer":{"title":"takes\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si696546","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_86","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide696601q39","for":"Slide696601q39"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696560","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_87","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide696601q39","for":"Slide696601q39"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696591","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_46","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide696601q39"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide696601","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si696602","si696418","si696439","si696463","si696474","si696485","si696496","si696507","si696546","si696560","si696591"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide696601"},"question":{"interactionId":"696365","quizId":382,"title":"Question 15\r","text":"He _______ along really well with his sister. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si696876","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide696875q40"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696692","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_519","title":"Harry’s worried ________ his driving test tomorrow.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696713","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_520","title":"Question 16 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696733","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_561","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696737","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_562","title":"in ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696733_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_234","roles":{"answer":{"title":"in\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si696744","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_563","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696748","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_564","title":"about ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696744_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_235","roles":{"answer":{"title":"about\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si696755","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_565","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696759","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_566","title":"at ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696755_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_236","roles":{"answer":{"title":"at\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si696766","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_567","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696770","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_568","title":"of ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696766_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_237","roles":{"answer":{"title":"of\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si696777","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_569","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696781","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_570","title":"for ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696777_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_238","roles":{"answer":{"title":"for\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si696820","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_88","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide696875q40","for":"Slide696875q40"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696834","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_89","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide696875q40","for":"Slide696875q40"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696865","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_47","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide696875q40"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide696875","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si696876","si696692","si696713","si696737","si696748","si696759","si696770","si696781","si696820","si696834","si696865"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide696875"},"question":{"interactionId":"696639","quizId":382,"title":"Question 16\r","text":"Harry’s worried ________ his driving test tomorrow. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si697150","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide697149q41"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696966","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_571","title":"Don’t _________ so much noise! I’m trying to study. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si696987","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_572","title":"Question 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697007","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_573","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697011","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_574","title":"do ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697007_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_239","roles":{"answer":{"title":"do\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si697018","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_575","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697022","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_576","title":"have ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697018_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_240","roles":{"answer":{"title":"have\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si697029","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_577","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697033","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_578","title":"make ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697029_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_241","roles":{"answer":{"title":"make\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si697040","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_579","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697044","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_580","title":"get ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697040_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_242","roles":{"answer":{"title":"get\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si697051","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_581","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697055","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_582","title":"take ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697051_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_243","roles":{"answer":{"title":"take\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si697094","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_90","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide697149q41","for":"Slide697149q41"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_91","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide697149q41","for":"Slide697149q41"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697139","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_48","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide697149q41"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide697149","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si697150","si696966","si696987","si697011","si697022","si697033","si697044","si697055","si697094","si697108","si697139"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide697149"},"question":{"interactionId":"696913","quizId":382,"title":"Question 17\r","text":"Don’t _________ so much noise! I’m trying to study.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si697424","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide697423q42"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697240","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_583","title":"When I was a little girl, I ________ my bike every day. Now I don’t anymore. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697261","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_584","title":"Question 18 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697281","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_585","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697285","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_586","title":"used to ride ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697281_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_244","roles":{"answer":{"title":"used to ride\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si697292","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_587","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697296","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_588","title":"use to ride ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697292_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_245","roles":{"answer":{"title":"use to ride\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si697303","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_589","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697307","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_590","title":"was riding ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697303_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_246","roles":{"answer":{"title":"was riding\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si697314","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_591","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697318","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_592","title":"would to ride ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697314_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_247","roles":{"answer":{"title":"would to ride\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si697325","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_593","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697329","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_594","title":"was used to ride ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697325_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_248","roles":{"answer":{"title":"was used to ride\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si697368","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_92","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide697423q42","for":"Slide697423q42"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_93","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide697423q42","for":"Slide697423q42"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697413","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_49","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide697423q42"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide697423","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si697424","si697240","si697261","si697285","si697296","si697307","si697318","si697329","si697368","si697382","si697413"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide697423"},"question":{"interactionId":"697187","quizId":382,"title":"Question 18\r","text":"When I was a little girl, I ________ my bike every day. Now I don’t anymore.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_221","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_221","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687400","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687411","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_173","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_173","title":"End of Section A2+/B1- ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide687456","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_221","si687400","si687411","Text_Caption_173"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide687456"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_206","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_206","title":"IR ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si686860","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"IR ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si686871","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"IR ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_170","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_170","title":"Section B1+/B2- ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_207","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_207","title":"Esta parte do teste tem 18 perguntas. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_208","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_208","title":"Você precisa de pelo menos 60% para passar para a próxima parte. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_209","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_209","title":"Você deve responder a cada pergunta e não pode voltar depois de enviar suas respostas. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_210","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_210","title":"Boa sorte!  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_211","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_211","title":"You’re On A Roll! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_212","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_212","title":"Oh Yeah!  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_135","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_135","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_137","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_137","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide686984","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_206","si686860","si686871","Text_Caption_170","SmartShape_207","SmartShape_208","SmartShape_209","SmartShape_210","SmartShape_211","SmartShape_212","Image_135","Image_137"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":630},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide686984"}}},{"id":"si697698","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide697697q43"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697514","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_595","title":"If I _________ $20 on the floor in a store, I ________ it to one of the assistants. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697535","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_596","title":"Question 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697555","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_597","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697559","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_598","title":"had found -- would be given ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697555_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_249","roles":{"answer":{"title":"had found -- would be given\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si697566","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_599","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697570","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_600","title":"find -- would give ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697566_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_250","roles":{"answer":{"title":"find -- would give\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si697577","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_601","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697581","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_602","title":"had found -- will give ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697577_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_251","roles":{"answer":{"title":"had found -- will give\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si697588","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_603","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697592","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_604","title":"found -- would give ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697588_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_252","roles":{"answer":{"title":"found -- would give\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si697599","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_605","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697603","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_606","title":"would find -- gave ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697599_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_253","roles":{"answer":{"title":"would find -- gave\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si697642","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_94","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide697697q43","for":"Slide697697q43"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697656","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_95","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide697697q43","for":"Slide697697q43"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697687","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_50","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide697697q43"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide697697","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si697698","si697514","si697535","si697559","si697570","si697581","si697592","si697603","si697642","si697656","si697687"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide697697"},"question":{"interactionId":"697461","quizId":382,"title":"Question 1\r","text":"If I _________ $20 on the floor in a store, I ________ it to one of the assistants.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si697972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide697971q44"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697788","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_607","title":"Wait until Roberto ________ here and then we can start the meeting.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697809","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_608","title":"Question 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697829","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_609","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697833","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_610","title":"got  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697829_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_254","roles":{"answer":{"title":"got \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si697840","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_611","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697844","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_612","title":"will get ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697840_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_255","roles":{"answer":{"title":"will get\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si697851","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_613","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697855","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_614","title":"is going to get ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697851_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_256","roles":{"answer":{"title":"is going to get\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si697862","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_615","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697866","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_616","title":"gets  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697862_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_257","roles":{"answer":{"title":"gets \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si697873","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_617","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697877","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_618","title":"will got ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697873_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_258","roles":{"answer":{"title":"will got\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si697916","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_96","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide697971q44","for":"Slide697971q44"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697930","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_97","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide697971q44","for":"Slide697971q44"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si697961","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_51","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide697971q44"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide697971","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si697972","si697788","si697809","si697833","si697844","si697855","si697866","si697877","si697916","si697930","si697961"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide697971"},"question":{"interactionId":"697735","quizId":382,"title":"Question 2\r","text":"Wait until Roberto ________ here and then we can start the meeting. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si698463","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide698462q45"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698279","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_621","title":"I ________ less coffee for the last few months to see if it helps with my headaches.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698300","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_620","title":"Question 3 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698320","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_630","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698324","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_631","title":"’ve been drinking ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698320_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_268","roles":{"answer":{"title":"’ve been drinking\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si698331","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_632","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698335","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_633","title":"was drinking ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698331_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_269","roles":{"answer":{"title":"was drinking\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si698342","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_634","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698346","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_635","title":"am drinking ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698342_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_270","roles":{"answer":{"title":"am drinking\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si698353","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_636","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698357","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_637","title":"drink ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698353_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_271","roles":{"answer":{"title":"drink\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si698364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_638","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698368","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_639","title":"drank ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698364_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_272","roles":{"answer":{"title":"drank\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si698407","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_99","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide698462q45","for":"Slide698462q45"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698421","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_100","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide698462q45","for":"Slide698462q45"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698452","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_53","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide698462q45"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide698462","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si698463","si698279","si698300","si698324","si698335","si698346","si698357","si698368","si698407","si698421","si698452"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide698462"},"question":{"interactionId":"698226","quizId":382,"title":"Question 3\r","text":"I ________ less coffee for the last few months to see if it helps with my headaches. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si698737","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide698736q46"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698553","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_622","title":"I would have invited you to the party if I ______ you were around! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698574","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_623","title":"Question 4 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698594","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_640","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698598","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_641","title":"have known ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698594_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_273","roles":{"answer":{"title":"have known\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si698605","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_642","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698609","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_643","title":"had known ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698605_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_274","roles":{"answer":{"title":"had known\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si698616","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_644","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698620","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_645","title":"was known ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698616_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_275","roles":{"answer":{"title":"was known\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si698627","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_646","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698631","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_647","title":"know ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698627_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_276","roles":{"answer":{"title":"know\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si698638","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_648","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698642","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_649","title":"was knowing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698638_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_277","roles":{"answer":{"title":"was knowing\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si698681","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_101","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide698736q46","for":"Slide698736q46"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698695","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_102","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide698736q46","for":"Slide698736q46"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698726","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_54","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide698736q46"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide698736","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si698737","si698553","si698574","si698598","si698609","si698620","si698631","si698642","si698681","si698695","si698726"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide698736"},"question":{"interactionId":"698500","quizId":382,"title":"Question 4\r","text":"I would have invited you to the party if I ______ you were around!\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si699011","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide699010q47"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698827","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_624","title":"A: Didn’t you hear your phone ring? B: No I _________ to music with my headphones on. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698848","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_625","title":"Question 5 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698868","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_650","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698872","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_651","title":"have listened ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698868_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_278","roles":{"answer":{"title":"have listened\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si698879","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_652","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698883","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_653","title":"had listened ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698879_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_279","roles":{"answer":{"title":"had listened\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si698890","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_654","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698894","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_655","title":"was listening ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698890_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_280","roles":{"answer":{"title":"was listening\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si698901","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_656","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698905","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_657","title":"had been listening ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698901_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_281","roles":{"answer":{"title":"had been listening\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si698912","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_658","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698916","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_659","title":"would be listening ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698912_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_282","roles":{"answer":{"title":"would be listening\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si698955","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_103","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide699010q47","for":"Slide699010q47"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si698969","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_104","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide699010q47","for":"Slide699010q47"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699000","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_55","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide699010q47"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide699010","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si699011","si698827","si698848","si698872","si698883","si698894","si698905","si698916","si698955","si698969","si699000"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide699010"},"question":{"interactionId":"698774","quizId":382,"title":"Question 5\r","text":"A: Didn’t you hear your phone ring?\rB: No I _________ to music with my headphones on.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si699559","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide699558q48"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699375","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_628","title":"It won’t take long to paint this room, ______ it? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699396","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_629","title":"Question 6 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699416","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_670","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699420","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_671","title":"isn’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699416_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_288","roles":{"answer":{"title":"isn’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si699427","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_672","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699431","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_673","title":"won’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699427_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_289","roles":{"answer":{"title":"won’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si699438","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_674","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699442","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_675","title":"does ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699438_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_290","roles":{"answer":{"title":"does\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si699449","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_676","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699453","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_677","title":"will ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699449_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_291","roles":{"answer":{"title":"will\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si699460","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_678","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699464","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_679","title":"don’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699460_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_292","roles":{"answer":{"title":"don’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si699503","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_107","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide699558q48","for":"Slide699558q48"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699517","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_108","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide699558q48","for":"Slide699558q48"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699548","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_57","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide699558q48"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide699558","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si699559","si699375","si699396","si699420","si699431","si699442","si699453","si699464","si699503","si699517","si699548"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide699558"},"question":{"interactionId":"699322","quizId":382,"title":"Question 6\r","text":"It won’t take long to paint this room, ______ it?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si699833","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide699832q49"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699649","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_660","title":"You wouldn’t have missed the train if you _________ in bed so long. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699670","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_661","title":"Question 7 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699690","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_680","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699694","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_681","title":"hadn’t stayed ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699690_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_293","roles":{"answer":{"title":"hadn’t stayed\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si699701","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_682","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699705","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_683","title":"don’t stay ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699701_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_294","roles":{"answer":{"title":"don’t stay\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si699712","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_684","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699716","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_685","title":"stayed ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699712_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_295","roles":{"answer":{"title":"stayed\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si699723","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_686","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699727","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_687","title":"wouldn’t stay ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699723_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_296","roles":{"answer":{"title":"wouldn’t stay\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si699734","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_688","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_689","title":"haven’t stayed ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699734_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_297","roles":{"answer":{"title":"haven’t stayed\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si699777","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_109","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide699832q49","for":"Slide699832q49"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699791","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_110","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide699832q49","for":"Slide699832q49"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699822","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_58","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide699832q49"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide699832","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si699833","si699649","si699670","si699694","si699705","si699716","si699727","si699738","si699777","si699791","si699822"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide699832"},"question":{"interactionId":"699596","quizId":382,"title":"Question 7\r","text":"You wouldn’t have missed the train if you _________ in bed so long.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si700107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide700106q50"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699923","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_662","title":"You’re Andy’s new secretary, ______ you? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699944","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_663","title":"Question 8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699964","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_690","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699968","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_691","title":"are ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699964_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_298","roles":{"answer":{"title":"are\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si699975","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_692","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699979","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_693","title":"don’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699975_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_299","roles":{"answer":{"title":"don’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si699986","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_694","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699990","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_695","title":"won’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699986_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_300","roles":{"answer":{"title":"won’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si699997","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_696","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700001","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_697","title":"do ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si699997_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_301","roles":{"answer":{"title":"do\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si700008","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_698","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700012","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_699","title":"aren’t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700008_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_302","roles":{"answer":{"title":"aren’t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si700051","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_111","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide700106q50","for":"Slide700106q50"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700065","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_112","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide700106q50","for":"Slide700106q50"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700096","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_59","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide700106q50"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide700106","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si700107","si699923","si699944","si699968","si699979","si699990","si700001","si700012","si700051","si700065","si700096"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide700106"},"question":{"interactionId":"699870","quizId":382,"title":"Question 8\r","text":"You’re Andy’s new secretary, ______ you?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si700381","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide700380q51"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700197","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_664","title":"That’s the man _____ dog bit me last month! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700218","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_665","title":"Question 9 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700238","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_700","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700242","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_701","title":"who’s ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700238_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_303","roles":{"answer":{"title":"who’s\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si700249","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_702","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700253","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_703","title":"whose ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700249_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_304","roles":{"answer":{"title":"whose\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si700260","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_704","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700264","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_705","title":"his ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700260_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_305","roles":{"answer":{"title":"his\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si700271","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_706","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700275","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_707","title":"that ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700271_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_306","roles":{"answer":{"title":"that\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si700282","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_708","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700286","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_709","title":"what ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700282_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_307","roles":{"answer":{"title":"what\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si700325","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_113","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide700380q51","for":"Slide700380q51"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700339","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_114","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide700380q51","for":"Slide700380q51"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700370","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_60","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide700380q51"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide700380","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si700381","si700197","si700218","si700242","si700253","si700264","si700275","si700286","si700325","si700339","si700370"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide700380"},"question":{"interactionId":"700144","quizId":382,"title":"Question 9\r","text":"That’s the man _____ dog bit me last month!\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si700655","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide700654q52"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700471","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_666","title":"There were very _______ people at the concert because of the bad weather. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700492","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_667","title":"Question 10 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700512","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_710","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700516","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_711","title":"little ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700512_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_308","roles":{"answer":{"title":"little\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si700523","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_712","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700527","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_713","title":"few ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700523_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_309","roles":{"answer":{"title":"few\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si700534","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_714","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700538","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_715","title":"much ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700534_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_310","roles":{"answer":{"title":"much\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si700545","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_716","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700549","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_717","title":"lots ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700545_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_311","roles":{"answer":{"title":"lots\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si700556","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_718","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700560","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_719","title":"many ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700556_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_312","roles":{"answer":{"title":"many\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si700599","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_115","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide700654q52","for":"Slide700654q52"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700613","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_116","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide700654q52","for":"Slide700654q52"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700644","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_61","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide700654q52"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide700654","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si700655","si700471","si700492","si700516","si700527","si700538","si700549","si700560","si700599","si700613","si700644"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide700654"},"question":{"interactionId":"700418","quizId":382,"title":"Question 10\r","text":"There were very _______ people at the concert because of the bad weather.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si700929","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide700928q53"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700745","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_668","title":"You won’t be able to get home ______ you call a taxi. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700766","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_669","title":"Question 11 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700786","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_720","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700790","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_721","title":"unless ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700786_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_313","roles":{"answer":{"title":"unless\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si700797","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_722","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700801","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_723","title":"however ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700797_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_314","roles":{"answer":{"title":"however\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si700808","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_724","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700812","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_725","title":"if ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700808_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_315","roles":{"answer":{"title":"if\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si700819","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_726","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700823","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_727","title":"although ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700819_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_316","roles":{"answer":{"title":"although\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si700830","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_728","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700834","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_729","title":"moreover ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700830_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_317","roles":{"answer":{"title":"moreover\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si700873","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_117","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide700928q53","for":"Slide700928q53"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700887","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_118","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide700928q53","for":"Slide700928q53"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si700918","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_62","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide700928q53"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide700928","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si700929","si700745","si700766","si700790","si700801","si700812","si700823","si700834","si700873","si700887","si700918"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide700928"},"question":{"interactionId":"700692","quizId":382,"title":"Question 11\r","text":"You won’t be able to get home ______ you call a taxi.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si701203","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide701202q54"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701019","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_730","title":"The Olympics ________ in London in 2012. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701040","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_731","title":"Question 12 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701060","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_732","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701064","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_733","title":"held ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701060_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_318","roles":{"answer":{"title":"held\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si701071","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_734","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701075","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_735","title":"would be going to be held ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701071_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_319","roles":{"answer":{"title":"would be going to be held\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si701082","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_736","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701086","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_737","title":"were held ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701082_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_320","roles":{"answer":{"title":"were held\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si701093","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_738","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701097","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_739","title":"were going to hold ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701093_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_321","roles":{"answer":{"title":"were going to hold\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si701104","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_740","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_741","title":"had held ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701104_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_322","roles":{"answer":{"title":"had held\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si701147","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_119","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide701202q54","for":"Slide701202q54"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701161","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_120","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide701202q54","for":"Slide701202q54"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701192","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_63","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide701202q54"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide701202","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si701203","si701019","si701040","si701064","si701075","si701086","si701097","si701108","si701147","si701161","si701192"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide701202"},"question":{"interactionId":"700966","quizId":382,"title":"Question 12\r","text":"The Olympics ________ in London in 2012.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si701477","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide701476q55"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701293","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_742","title":"Brazil is famous _______ its beaches.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701314","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_743","title":"Question 13 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701334","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_744","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701338","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_745","title":"as ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701334_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_323","roles":{"answer":{"title":"as\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si701345","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_746","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_747","title":"at ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701345_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_324","roles":{"answer":{"title":"at\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si701356","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_748","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701360","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_749","title":"because ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701356_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_325","roles":{"answer":{"title":"because\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si701367","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_750","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701371","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_751","title":"for ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701367_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_326","roles":{"answer":{"title":"for\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si701378","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_752","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_753","title":"due ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701378_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_327","roles":{"answer":{"title":"due\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si701421","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_121","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide701476q55","for":"Slide701476q55"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_122","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide701476q55","for":"Slide701476q55"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701466","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_64","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide701476q55"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide701476","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si701477","si701293","si701314","si701338","si701349","si701360","si701371","si701382","si701421","si701435","si701466"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide701476"},"question":{"interactionId":"701240","quizId":382,"title":"Question 13\r","text":"Brazil is famous _______ its beaches. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si701751","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide701750q56"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701567","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_754","title":"I got a 10% _______ on the coat because it had a button missing.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701588","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_755","title":"Question 14 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701608","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_756","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701612","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_757","title":"refund ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701608_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_328","roles":{"answer":{"title":"refund\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si701619","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_758","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701623","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_759","title":"bargain ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701619_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_329","roles":{"answer":{"title":"bargain\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si701630","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_760","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701634","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_761","title":"off ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701630_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_330","roles":{"answer":{"title":"off\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si701641","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_762","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701645","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_763","title":"out ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701641_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_331","roles":{"answer":{"title":"out\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si701652","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_764","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701656","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_765","title":"discount ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701652_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_332","roles":{"answer":{"title":"discount\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si701695","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_123","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide701750q56","for":"Slide701750q56"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701709","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_124","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide701750q56","for":"Slide701750q56"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701740","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_65","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide701750q56"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide701750","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si701751","si701567","si701588","si701612","si701623","si701634","si701645","si701656","si701695","si701709","si701740"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide701750"},"question":{"interactionId":"701514","quizId":382,"title":"Question 14\r","text":"I got a 10% _______ on the coat because it had a button missing. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si702025","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide702024q57"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701841","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_766","title":"It was very ______ that Jeff drove past and picked us up just after we’d missed the bus. Otherwise, we would’ve had to walk.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701862","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_767","title":"Question 15 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701882","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_768","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701886","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_769","title":"fortune ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701882_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_333","roles":{"answer":{"title":"fortune\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si701893","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_770","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701897","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_771","title":"fortunate ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701893_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_334","roles":{"answer":{"title":"fortunate\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si701904","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_772","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701908","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_773","title":"fortunately ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701904_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_335","roles":{"answer":{"title":"fortunately\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si701915","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_774","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701919","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_775","title":"unfortunate ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701915_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_336","roles":{"answer":{"title":"unfortunate\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si701926","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_776","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701930","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_777","title":"unfortunately ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701926_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_337","roles":{"answer":{"title":"unfortunately\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si701969","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_125","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide702024q57","for":"Slide702024q57"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si701983","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_126","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide702024q57","for":"Slide702024q57"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702014","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_66","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide702024q57"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide702024","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si702025","si701841","si701862","si701886","si701897","si701908","si701919","si701930","si701969","si701983","si702014"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide702024"},"question":{"interactionId":"701788","quizId":382,"title":"Question 15\r","text":"It was very ______ that Jeff drove past and picked us up just after we’d missed the bus. Otherwise, we would’ve had to walk. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si702790","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide702789q58"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702606","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_802","title":"The reporter asked the actor what ___________________. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702627","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_803","title":"Question 16 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702647","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_804","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702651","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_805","title":"was the most interesting role he had played ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702647_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_352","roles":{"answer":{"title":"was the most interesting role he had played\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si702658","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_806","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702662","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_807","title":"the most interesting role he had played was ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702658_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_353","roles":{"answer":{"title":"the most interesting role he had played was\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si702669","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_808","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702673","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_809","title":"role he had played was the most interesting ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702669_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_354","roles":{"answer":{"title":"role he had played was the most interesting\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si702680","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_810","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702684","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_811","title":"was the most interesting role he ever played ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702680_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_355","roles":{"answer":{"title":"was the most interesting role he ever played\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si702691","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_812","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702695","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_813","title":"were the most interesting role he had ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702691_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_356","roles":{"answer":{"title":"were the most interesting role he had\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si702734","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_131","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide702789q58","for":"Slide702789q58"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702748","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_132","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide702789q58","for":"Slide702789q58"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702779","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_69","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide702789q58"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide702789","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si702790","si702606","si702627","si702651","si702662","si702673","si702684","si702695","si702734","si702748","si702779"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide702789"},"question":{"interactionId":"702553","quizId":382,"title":"Question 16\r","text":"The reporter asked the actor what ___________________.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si703064","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide703063q59"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702880","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_814","title":"Her parents aren’t strict enough with her. They let her ______ whatever she likes.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702901","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_815","title":"Question 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702921","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_816","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702925","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_817","title":"do ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702921_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_357","roles":{"answer":{"title":"do\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si702932","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_818","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702936","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_819","title":"to do ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702932_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_358","roles":{"answer":{"title":"to do\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si702943","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_820","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702947","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_821","title":"doing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702943_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_359","roles":{"answer":{"title":"doing\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si702954","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_822","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702958","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_823","title":"being done ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702954_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_360","roles":{"answer":{"title":"being done\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si702965","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_824","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702969","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_825","title":"to doing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si702965_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_361","roles":{"answer":{"title":"to doing\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si703008","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_133","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide703063q59","for":"Slide703063q59"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703022","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_134","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide703063q59","for":"Slide703063q59"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703053","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_70","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide703063q59"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide703063","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si703064","si702880","si702901","si702925","si702936","si702947","si702958","si702969","si703008","si703022","si703053"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide703063"},"question":{"interactionId":"702827","quizId":382,"title":"Question 17\r","text":"Her parents aren’t strict enough with her. They let her ______ whatever she likes. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si703338","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide703337q60"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703154","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_826","title":"We decided _______ her birthday present because we weren’t sure what she wanted.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703175","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_827","title":"Question 18 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703195","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_828","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703199","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_829","title":"not buying ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703195_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_362","roles":{"answer":{"title":"not buying\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si703206","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_830","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703210","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_831","title":"not buy ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703206_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_363","roles":{"answer":{"title":"not buy\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si703217","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_832","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703221","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_833","title":"not to buy ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703217_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_364","roles":{"answer":{"title":"not to buy\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si703228","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_834","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703232","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_835","title":"don’t buy ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703228_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_365","roles":{"answer":{"title":"don’t buy\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si703239","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_836","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703243","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_837","title":"didn’t buy ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703239_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_366","roles":{"answer":{"title":"didn’t buy\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si703282","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_135","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide703337q60","for":"Slide703337q60"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703296","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_136","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide703337q60","for":"Slide703337q60"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703327","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_71","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide703337q60"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide703337","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si703338","si703154","si703175","si703199","si703210","si703221","si703232","si703243","si703282","si703296","si703327"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide703337"},"question":{"interactionId":"703101","quizId":382,"title":"Question 18\r","text":"We decided _______ her birthday present because we weren’t sure what she wanted. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_222","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_222","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687514","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687525","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_174","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_174","title":"End of Section B1-/B2+ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide687570","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_222","si687514","si687525","Text_Caption_174"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide687570"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_213","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_213","title":"IR ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687060","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"IR ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687071","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"IR ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_171","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_171","title":"Section B2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_214","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_214","title":"Esta parte do teste tem 20 perguntas. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_215","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_215","title":"Você precisa de pelo menos 60% para passar para a próxima parte. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_216","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_216","title":"Você deve responder a cada pergunta e não pode voltar depois de enviar suas respostas. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_217","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_217","title":"Boa sorte!  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_218","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_218","title":"Last One! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_219","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_219","title":"Wiahhhhh! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_138","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_138","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_140","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_140","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide687184","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_213","si687060","si687071","Text_Caption_171","SmartShape_214","SmartShape_215","SmartShape_216","SmartShape_217","SmartShape_218","SmartShape_219","Image_138","Image_140"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":624},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide687184"}}},{"id":"si703612","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide703611q61"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703428","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_838","title":"Could you tell me _______________? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703449","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_839","title":"Question 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703469","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_840","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_841","title":"how much does this book cost ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703469_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_367","roles":{"answer":{"title":"how much does this book cost\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si703480","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_842","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703484","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_843","title":"how much this book costs ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703480_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_368","roles":{"answer":{"title":"how much this book costs\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si703491","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_844","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703495","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_845","title":"how much does this book ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703491_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_369","roles":{"answer":{"title":"how much does this book\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si703502","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_846","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703506","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_847","title":"how much does this book costs ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703502_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_370","roles":{"answer":{"title":"how much does this book costs\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si703513","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_848","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703517","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_849","title":"how much is this book cost ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703513_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_371","roles":{"answer":{"title":"how much is this book cost\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si703556","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_137","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide703611q61","for":"Slide703611q61"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703570","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_138","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide703611q61","for":"Slide703611q61"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703601","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_72","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide703611q61"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide703611","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si703612","si703428","si703449","si703473","si703484","si703495","si703506","si703517","si703556","si703570","si703601"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide703611"},"question":{"interactionId":"703375","quizId":382,"title":"Question 1\r","text":"Could you tell me _______________?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si703886","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide703885q62"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703702","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_850","title":"Your boss ___________ three times this morning. I think it’s urgent. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703723","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_851","title":"Question 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703743","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_852","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703747","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_853","title":"has been calling ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703743_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_372","roles":{"answer":{"title":"has been calling\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si703754","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_854","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703758","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_855","title":"calls ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703754_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_373","roles":{"answer":{"title":"calls\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si703765","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_856","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703769","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_857","title":"is calling ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703765_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_374","roles":{"answer":{"title":"is calling\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si703776","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_858","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703780","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_859","title":"has called ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703776_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_375","roles":{"answer":{"title":"has called\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si703787","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_860","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703791","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_861","title":"was calling ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703787_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_376","roles":{"answer":{"title":"was calling\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si703830","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_139","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide703885q62","for":"Slide703885q62"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703844","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_140","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide703885q62","for":"Slide703885q62"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703875","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_73","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide703885q62"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide703885","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si703886","si703702","si703723","si703747","si703758","si703769","si703780","si703791","si703830","si703844","si703875"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide703885"},"question":{"interactionId":"703649","quizId":382,"title":"Question 2\r","text":"Your boss ___________ three times this morning. I think it’s urgent.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si704160","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide704159q63"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703976","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_862","title":"They live in a/an ______________. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si703997","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_863","title":"Question 3 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704017","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_864","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704021","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_865","title":"big charming old house ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704017_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_377","roles":{"answer":{"title":"big charming old house\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si704028","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_866","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704032","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_867","title":"house charming big old ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704028_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_378","roles":{"answer":{"title":"house charming big old\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si704039","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_868","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704043","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_869","title":"old charming big house ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704039_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_379","roles":{"answer":{"title":"old charming big house\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si704050","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_870","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704054","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_871","title":"big house old charming ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704050_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_380","roles":{"answer":{"title":"big house old charming\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si704061","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_872","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704065","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_873","title":"charming big old house ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704061_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_381","roles":{"answer":{"title":"charming big old house\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si704104","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_141","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide704159q63","for":"Slide704159q63"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704118","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_142","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide704159q63","for":"Slide704159q63"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704149","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_74","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide704159q63"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide704159","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si704160","si703976","si703997","si704021","si704032","si704043","si704054","si704065","si704104","si704118","si704149"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide704159"},"question":{"interactionId":"703923","quizId":382,"title":"Question 3\r","text":"They live in a/an ______________.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si704434","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide704433q64"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704250","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_874","title":"Murderers ______________ to life imprisonment. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704271","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_875","title":"Question 4 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704291","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_876","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704295","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_877","title":"are usually sentenced ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704291_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_382","roles":{"answer":{"title":"are usually sentenced\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si704302","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_878","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704306","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_879","title":"usually sentenced ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704302_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_383","roles":{"answer":{"title":"usually sentenced\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si704313","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_880","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704317","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_881","title":"are sentenced usually ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704313_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_384","roles":{"answer":{"title":"are sentenced usually\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si704324","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_882","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704328","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_883","title":"sentenced usually ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704324_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_385","roles":{"answer":{"title":"sentenced usually\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si704335","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_884","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704339","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_885","title":"sentenced are usually ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704335_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_386","roles":{"answer":{"title":"sentenced are usually\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si704378","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_143","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide704433q64","for":"Slide704433q64"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704392","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_144","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide704433q64","for":"Slide704433q64"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704423","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_75","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide704433q64"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide704433","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si704434","si704250","si704271","si704295","si704306","si704317","si704328","si704339","si704378","si704392","si704423"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide704433"},"question":{"interactionId":"704197","quizId":382,"title":"Question 4\r","text":"Murderers ______________ to life imprisonment.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si704708","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide704707q65"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704524","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_886","title":"He is thought __________ a bank. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704545","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_887","title":"Question 5 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704565","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_888","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704569","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_889","title":"have robbed ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704565_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_387","roles":{"answer":{"title":"have robbed\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si704576","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_890","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704580","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_891","title":"to have robbed ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704576_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_388","roles":{"answer":{"title":"to have robbed\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si704587","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_892","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704591","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_893","title":"to be robbed ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704587_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_389","roles":{"answer":{"title":"to be robbed\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si704598","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_894","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704602","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_895","title":"to rob ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704598_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_390","roles":{"answer":{"title":"to rob\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si704609","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_896","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704613","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_897","title":"robbing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704609_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_391","roles":{"answer":{"title":"robbing\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si704652","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_145","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide704707q65","for":"Slide704707q65"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704666","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_146","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide704707q65","for":"Slide704707q65"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704697","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_76","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide704707q65"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide704707","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si704708","si704524","si704545","si704569","si704580","si704591","si704602","si704613","si704652","si704666","si704697"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide704707"},"question":{"interactionId":"704471","quizId":382,"title":"Question 5\r","text":"He is thought __________ a bank.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si704982","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide704981q66"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704798","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_898","title":"Don’t worry. Rob __________ the exam if he studies enough.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704819","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_899","title":"Question 6 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704839","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_900","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704843","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_901","title":"passes ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704839_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_392","roles":{"answer":{"title":"passes\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si704850","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_902","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704854","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_903","title":"has passed ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704850_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_393","roles":{"answer":{"title":"has passed\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si704861","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_904","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704865","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_905","title":"will pass ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704861_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_394","roles":{"answer":{"title":"will pass\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si704872","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_906","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704876","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_907","title":"would pass ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704872_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_395","roles":{"answer":{"title":"would pass\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si704883","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_908","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704887","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_909","title":"is passing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704883_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_396","roles":{"answer":{"title":"is passing\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si704926","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_147","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide704981q66","for":"Slide704981q66"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704940","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_148","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide704981q66","for":"Slide704981q66"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si704971","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_77","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide704981q66"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide704981","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si704982","si704798","si704819","si704843","si704854","si704865","si704876","si704887","si704926","si704940","si704971"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide704981"},"question":{"interactionId":"704745","quizId":382,"title":"Question 6\r","text":"Don’t worry. Rob __________ the exam if he studies enough. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si705256","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide705255q67"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705072","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_910","title":"Don’t call Andrea now. If it’s eight o’clock, she _________ the baby a bath.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705093","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_911","title":"Question 7 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705113","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_912","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705117","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_913","title":"’ll give ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705113_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_397","roles":{"answer":{"title":"’ll give\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si705124","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_914","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705128","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_915","title":"’ll be giving ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705124_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_398","roles":{"answer":{"title":"’ll be giving\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si705135","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_916","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705139","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_917","title":"’ll have given ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705135_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_399","roles":{"answer":{"title":"’ll have given\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si705146","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_918","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705150","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_919","title":"gives ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705146_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_400","roles":{"answer":{"title":"gives\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si705157","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_920","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705161","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_921","title":"’ll giving ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705157_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_401","roles":{"answer":{"title":"’ll giving\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si705200","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_149","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide705255q67","for":"Slide705255q67"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705214","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_150","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide705255q67","for":"Slide705255q67"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705245","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_78","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide705255q67"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide705255","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si705256","si705072","si705093","si705117","si705128","si705139","si705150","si705161","si705200","si705214","si705245"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide705255"},"question":{"interactionId":"705019","quizId":382,"title":"Question 7\r","text":"Don’t call Andrea now. If it’s eight o’clock, she _________ the baby a bath. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si705530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide705529q68"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705346","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_922","title":"Take an umbrella ____________ it rains. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705367","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_923","title":"Question 8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705387","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_924","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705391","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_925","title":"when ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705387_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_402","roles":{"answer":{"title":"when\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si705398","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_926","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705402","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_927","title":"if ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705398_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_403","roles":{"answer":{"title":"if\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si705409","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_928","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705413","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_929","title":"unless ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705409_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_404","roles":{"answer":{"title":"unless\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si705420","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_930","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705424","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_931","title":"because ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705420_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_405","roles":{"answer":{"title":"because\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si705431","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_932","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_933","title":"in case ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705431_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_406","roles":{"answer":{"title":"in case\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si705474","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_151","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide705529q68","for":"Slide705529q68"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705488","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_152","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide705529q68","for":"Slide705529q68"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705519","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_79","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide705529q68"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide705529","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si705530","si705346","si705367","si705391","si705402","si705413","si705424","si705435","si705474","si705488","si705519"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide705529"},"question":{"interactionId":"705293","quizId":382,"title":"Question 8\r","text":"Take an umbrella ____________ it rains.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si705804","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide705803q69"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705620","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_934","title":"I didn’t wait another minute. I didn’t see you.  If I __________ another minute, I _____________ you. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705641","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_935","title":"Question 9 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705661","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_936","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705665","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_937","title":"had waited -- would have seen ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705661_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_407","roles":{"answer":{"title":"had waited -- would have seen\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si705672","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_938","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705676","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_939","title":"would have waited -- had seen ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705672_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_408","roles":{"answer":{"title":"would have waited -- had seen\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si705683","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_940","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705687","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_941","title":"waited -- would see you ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705683_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_409","roles":{"answer":{"title":"waited -- would see you\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si705694","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_942","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705698","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_943","title":"hadn’t waited -- would have seen ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705694_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_410","roles":{"answer":{"title":"hadn’t waited -- would have seen\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si705705","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_944","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705709","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_945","title":"would wait -- saw ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705705_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_411","roles":{"answer":{"title":"would wait -- saw\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si705748","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_153","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide705803q69","for":"Slide705803q69"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705762","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_154","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide705803q69","for":"Slide705803q69"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si705793","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_80","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide705803q69"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide705803","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si705804","si705620","si705641","si705665","si705676","si705687","si705698","si705709","si705748","si705762","si705793"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide705803"},"question":{"interactionId":"705567","quizId":382,"title":"Question 9\r","text":"I didn’t wait another minute. I didn’t see you. \rIf I __________ another minute, I _____________ you.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si706626","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide706625q70"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706442","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_959","title":"She ____________________. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706463","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_960","title":"Question 10 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706483","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_969","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706487","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_970","title":"looks if she’s been crying ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706483_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_422","roles":{"answer":{"title":"looks if she’s been crying\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si706494","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_971","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706498","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_972","title":"look likes she’s been crying ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706494_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_423","roles":{"answer":{"title":"look likes she’s been crying\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si706505","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_973","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706509","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_974","title":"looks as she’s been crying ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706505_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_424","roles":{"answer":{"title":"looks as she’s been crying\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si706516","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_975","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706520","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_976","title":"looks as if she’s been crying ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706516_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_425","roles":{"answer":{"title":"looks as if she’s been crying\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si706527","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_977","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706531","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_978","title":"looks as if she cries ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706527_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_426","roles":{"answer":{"title":"looks as if she cries\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si706570","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_158","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide706625q70","for":"Slide706625q70"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706584","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_159","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide706625q70","for":"Slide706625q70"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706615","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_83","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide706625q70"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide706625","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si706626","si706442","si706463","si706487","si706498","si706509","si706520","si706531","si706570","si706584","si706615"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide706625"},"question":{"interactionId":"706389","quizId":382,"title":"Question 10\r","text":"She ____________________.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si706900","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide706899q71"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706716","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_961","title":"I suggested ____________ a taxi so we wouldn’t be late. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706737","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_962","title":"Question 11 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706757","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_979","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706761","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_980","title":"calling ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706757_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_427","roles":{"answer":{"title":"calling\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si706768","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_981","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706772","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_982","title":"to call ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706768_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_428","roles":{"answer":{"title":"to call\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si706779","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_983","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706783","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_984","title":"being called ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706779_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_429","roles":{"answer":{"title":"being called\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si706790","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_985","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706794","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_986","title":"we called ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706790_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_430","roles":{"answer":{"title":"we called\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si706801","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_987","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706805","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_988","title":"we should to call ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706801_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_431","roles":{"answer":{"title":"we should to call\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si706844","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_160","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide706899q71","for":"Slide706899q71"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706858","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_161","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide706899q71","for":"Slide706899q71"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706889","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_84","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide706899q71"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide706899","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si706900","si706716","si706737","si706761","si706772","si706783","si706794","si706805","si706844","si706858","si706889"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide706899"},"question":{"interactionId":"706663","quizId":382,"title":"Question 11\r","text":"I suggested ____________ a taxi so we wouldn’t be late.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si707174","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide707173q72"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si706990","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_963","title":"Your hair ___________. It’s really long. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707011","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_964","title":"Question 12 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707031","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_989","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707035","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_990","title":"need to be cut ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707031_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_432","roles":{"answer":{"title":"need to be cut\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si707042","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_991","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707046","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_992","title":"needs cut ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707042_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_433","roles":{"answer":{"title":"needs cut\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si707053","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_993","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707057","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_994","title":"needs to cut ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707053_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_434","roles":{"answer":{"title":"needs to cut\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si707064","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_995","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707068","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_996","title":"needs to be cutting ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707064_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_435","roles":{"answer":{"title":"needs to be cutting\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si707075","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_997","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707079","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_998","title":"needs cutting ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707075_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_436","roles":{"answer":{"title":"needs cutting\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si707118","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_162","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide707173q72","for":"Slide707173q72"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_163","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide707173q72","for":"Slide707173q72"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707163","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_85","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide707173q72"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide707173","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si707174","si706990","si707011","si707035","si707046","si707057","si707068","si707079","si707118","si707132","si707163"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide707173"},"question":{"interactionId":"706937","quizId":382,"title":"Question 12\r","text":"Your hair ___________. It’s really long.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si707448","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide707447q73"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707264","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_965","title":"She tried ___________ the TV but she wasn’t able to. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707285","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_966","title":"Question 13 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707305","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_999","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707309","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1000","title":"fix  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707305_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_437","roles":{"answer":{"title":"fix \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si707316","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1001","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707320","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1002","title":"to fix ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707316_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_438","roles":{"answer":{"title":"to fix\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si707327","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1003","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707331","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1004","title":"fixing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707327_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_439","roles":{"answer":{"title":"fixing\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si707338","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1005","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707342","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1006","title":"to fixing ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707338_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_440","roles":{"answer":{"title":"to fixing\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si707349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1007","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707353","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1008","title":"to have fixed ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707349_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_441","roles":{"answer":{"title":"to have fixed\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si707392","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_164","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide707447q73","for":"Slide707447q73"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707406","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_165","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide707447q73","for":"Slide707447q73"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707437","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_86","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide707447q73"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide707447","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si707448","si707264","si707285","si707309","si707320","si707331","si707342","si707353","si707392","si707406","si707437"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide707447"},"question":{"interactionId":"707211","quizId":382,"title":"Question 13\r","text":"She tried ___________ the TV but she wasn’t able to.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si707722","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide707721q74"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707538","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_967","title":"I must have my keys somewhere. I can remember _________ the door this morning. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707559","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_968","title":"Question 14 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707579","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1009","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707583","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1010","title":"to lock ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707579_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_442","roles":{"answer":{"title":"to lock\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si707590","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1011","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707594","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1012","title":"locking ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707590_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_443","roles":{"answer":{"title":"locking\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si707601","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1013","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707605","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1014","title":"lock ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707601_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_444","roles":{"answer":{"title":"lock\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si707612","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1015","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707616","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1016","title":"locked ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707612_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_445","roles":{"answer":{"title":"locked\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si707623","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1017","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707627","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1018","title":"to locking ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707623_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_446","roles":{"answer":{"title":"to locking\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si707666","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_166","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide707721q74","for":"Slide707721q74"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707680","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_167","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide707721q74","for":"Slide707721q74"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707711","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_87","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide707721q74"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide707721","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si707722","si707538","si707559","si707583","si707594","si707605","si707616","si707627","si707666","si707680","si707711"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide707721"},"question":{"interactionId":"707485","quizId":382,"title":"Question 14\r","text":"I must have my keys somewhere. I can remember _________ the door this morning.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si707996","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide707995q75"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707812","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1019","title":"He’s from England, so he _____________ on the left. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707833","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1020","title":"Question 15 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707853","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1021","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707857","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1022","title":"is used to driving  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707853_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_447","roles":{"answer":{"title":"is used to driving \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si707864","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1023","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707868","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1024","title":"is used to drive ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707864_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_448","roles":{"answer":{"title":"is used to drive\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si707875","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1025","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707879","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1026","title":"used to driving ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707875_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_449","roles":{"answer":{"title":"used to driving\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si707886","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1027","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707890","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1028","title":"is used driving ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707886_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_450","roles":{"answer":{"title":"is used driving\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si707897","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1029","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707901","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1030","title":"is driving ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707897_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_451","roles":{"answer":{"title":"is driving\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si707940","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_168","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide707995q75","for":"Slide707995q75"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707954","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_169","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide707995q75","for":"Slide707995q75"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si707985","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_88","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide707995q75"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide707995","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si707996","si707812","si707833","si707857","si707868","si707879","si707890","si707901","si707940","si707954","si707985"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide707995"},"question":{"interactionId":"707759","quizId":382,"title":"Question 15\r","text":"He’s from England, so he _____________ on the left.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si708270","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide708269q76"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708086","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1031","title":"That’s the school ________________. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1032","title":"Question 16 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708127","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1033","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708131","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1034","title":"I told you ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708127_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_452","roles":{"answer":{"title":"I told you\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si708138","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1035","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708142","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1036","title":"that I told you  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708138_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_453","roles":{"answer":{"title":"that I told you \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si708149","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1037","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708153","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1038","title":"about I told you ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708149_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_454","roles":{"answer":{"title":"about I told you\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si708160","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1039","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708164","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1040","title":"I told you about ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708160_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_455","roles":{"answer":{"title":"I told you about\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si708171","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1041","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708175","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1042","title":"that I talked ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708171_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_456","roles":{"answer":{"title":"that I talked\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si708214","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_170","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide708269q76","for":"Slide708269q76"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708228","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_171","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide708269q76","for":"Slide708269q76"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708259","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_89","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide708269q76"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide708269","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si708270","si708086","si708107","si708131","si708142","si708153","si708164","si708175","si708214","si708228","si708259"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide708269"},"question":{"interactionId":"708033","quizId":382,"title":"Question 16\r","text":"That’s the school ________________.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si708544","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide708543q77"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708360","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1043","title":"I checked ______________ on my flight. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708381","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1044","title":"Question 17 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708401","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1045","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1046","title":"two luggages ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708401_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_457","roles":{"answer":{"title":"two luggages\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si708412","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1047","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708416","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1048","title":"two pieces of luggage ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708412_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_458","roles":{"answer":{"title":"two pieces of luggage\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si708423","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1049","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708427","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1050","title":"some luggages ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708423_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_459","roles":{"answer":{"title":"some luggages\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si708434","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1051","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708438","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1052","title":"any luggage ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708434_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_460","roles":{"answer":{"title":"any luggage\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si708445","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1053","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708449","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1054","title":"a pieces of luggage ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708445_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_461","roles":{"answer":{"title":"a pieces of luggage\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si708488","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_172","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide708543q77","for":"Slide708543q77"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708502","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_173","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide708543q77","for":"Slide708543q77"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708533","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_90","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide708543q77"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide708543","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si708544","si708360","si708381","si708405","si708416","si708427","si708438","si708449","si708488","si708502","si708533"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide708543"},"question":{"interactionId":"708307","quizId":382,"title":"Question 17\r","text":"I checked ______________ on my flight.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si708818","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide708817q78"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708634","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1055","title":"___________ of us can go out tonight. We’re all broke. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708655","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1056","title":"Question 18 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708675","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1057","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708679","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1058","title":"Any ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708675_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_462","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Any\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si708686","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1059","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708690","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1060","title":"Both ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708686_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_463","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Both\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si708697","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1061","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708701","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1062","title":"None ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708697_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_464","roles":{"answer":{"title":"None\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si708708","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1063","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708712","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1064","title":"Nobody ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708708_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_465","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Nobody\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si708719","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1065","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708723","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1066","title":"All ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708719_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_466","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si708762","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_174","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide708817q78","for":"Slide708817q78"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708776","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_175","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide708817q78","for":"Slide708817q78"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708807","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_91","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide708817q78"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide708817","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si708818","si708634","si708655","si708679","si708690","si708701","si708712","si708723","si708762","si708776","si708807"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide708817"},"question":{"interactionId":"708581","quizId":382,"title":"Question 18\r","text":"___________ of us can go out tonight. We’re all broke.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si709092","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide709091q79"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708908","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1067","title":"I wish I ____________ thinner. My clothes don’t fit me anymore! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708929","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1068","title":"Question 19 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708949","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1069","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708953","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1070","title":"were ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708949_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_467","roles":{"answer":{"title":"were\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si708960","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1071","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708964","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1072","title":"had ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708960_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_468","roles":{"answer":{"title":"had\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si708971","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1073","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708975","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1074","title":"am ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708971_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_469","roles":{"answer":{"title":"am\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si708982","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1075","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708986","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1076","title":"could have ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708982_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_470","roles":{"answer":{"title":"could have\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si708993","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1077","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708997","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1078","title":"have been ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si708993_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_471","roles":{"answer":{"title":"have been\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si709036","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_176","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide709091q79","for":"Slide709091q79"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si709050","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_177","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide709091q79","for":"Slide709091q79"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si709081","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_92","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide709091q79"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide709091","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si709092","si708908","si708929","si708953","si708964","si708975","si708986","si708997","si709036","si709050","si709081"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide709091"},"question":{"interactionId":"708855","quizId":382,"title":"Question 19\r","text":"I wish I ____________ thinner. My clothes don’t fit me anymore!\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si709366","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide709365q80"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si709182","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1079","title":"____________ of his age, he’s still very attractive. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si709203","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1080","title":"Question 20 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si709223","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1081","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si709227","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1082","title":"However ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si709223_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"61_472","roles":{"answer":{"title":"However\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si709234","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1083","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si709238","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1084","title":"Even though ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si709234_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"64_473","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Even though\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si709245","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1085","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si709249","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1086","title":"Although ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si709245_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"66_474","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Although\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si709256","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1087","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si709260","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1088","title":"In spite ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si709256_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"68_475","roles":{"answer":{"title":"In spite\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si709267","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1089","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si709271","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1090","title":"Nonetheless ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si709267_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"70_476","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Nonetheless\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si709310","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_178","title":"Ir ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide709365q80","for":"Slide709365q80"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si709324","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_179","title":"Limpar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide709365q80","for":"Slide709365q80"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si709355","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_93","title":"Você deve responder antes de continuar. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide709365q80"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide709365","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si709366","si709182","si709203","si709227","si709238","si709249","si709260","si709271","si709310","si709324","si709355"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide709365"},"question":{"interactionId":"709129","quizId":382,"title":"Question 20\r","text":"____________ of his age, he’s still very attractive.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_223","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_223","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687628","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si687639","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_175","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_175","title":"End of Section B2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide687684","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_223","si687628","si687639","Text_Caption_175"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide687684"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_63","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_63","title":"Nome  Sobrenome:  Telefone:  Email:   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_142","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_142","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si548502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_144","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_144","title":"Please Fill In All The Information ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si553640","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Por Favor, Preencha Todos os Campos para Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si548514","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_92","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_92","title":"Por favor, preencha corretamente os campos abaixo para receber o resultado do seu teste ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Name","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Name","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Last_Name","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Last_Name","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Email","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Email","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Pone","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Pone","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Slide547673","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_63","SmartShape_142","si548502","SmartShape_144","si553640","si548514","Text_Caption_92","Name","Last_Name","Email","Pone"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":195},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide547673"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_96","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_96","title":" Unidade Bosque**      (12) 3322-2231  Av. Andromeda, 3671 -   Bosque, São José dos Campos - SP  contato-satelite@cbaidiomas.com ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_92","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_92","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_97","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_97","title":" Unidade Jd. Esplanada     (12) 3322-0016  Av. Barão do Rio Branco, 895 -   Jd. Esplanada, São José dos Campos - SP  contato-esplanada@cbaidiomas.com ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_93","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_93","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_98","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_98","title":" Unidade Jd. das Indústrias     (12) 3204-5320  Av. Dr. João B. S. de Queiroz, 911 -   Jd. das Indústrias, São José dos Campos - SP  contato-jdindustrias@cbaidiomas.com ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_94","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_94","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_162","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_162","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si664459","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si664479","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"ESPCheck","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"ESPCheck","roles":{}},{"id":"si664616","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"EspBox","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"EspBox","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Esplanada","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Esplanada","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_165","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_165","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"JArdim_Check","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"JArdim_Check","roles":{}},{"id":"si664606","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Jardim","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Jardim","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_163","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_163","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"BosqueCheck","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"BosqueCheck","roles":{}},{"id":"si664611","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Select_Message","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Select_Message","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_181","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_181","title":" **Selecone Bosque para fazer aula online ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_129","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_129","title":"Quais as unidades CBA de sua preferência? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si664702","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Selecione uma ou mais opções ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Bosque","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Bosque","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide646629","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_96","Image_92","Text_Caption_97","Image_93","Text_Caption_98","Image_94","SmartShape_162","si664459","si664479","ESPCheck","si664616","EspBox","Esplanada","SmartShape_165","JArdim_Check","si664606","Jardim","SmartShape_163","BosqueCheck","si664611","Select_Message","SmartShape_181","Text_Caption_129","si664702","Bosque"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":117},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide646629"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_110","title":" Manha - a partir de 7:30 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_111","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_111","title":" Tarde - a partir de 14:00    ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_112","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_112","title":" Noite - a partir de 18:00     ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_174","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_174","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si670517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si670528","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Afternooncheck","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Afternooncheck","roles":{}},{"id":"si670539","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"EspBox_175","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"EspBox_175","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Afternoonbox","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Afternoonbox","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_176","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_176","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Nightcheck","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Nightcheck","roles":{}},{"id":"si670588","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Nightbox","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Nightbox","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Select_Message_113","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Select_Message_113","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si670637","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Selecione uma ou mais opções ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_177","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_177","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Morningcheck","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Morningcheck","roles":{}},{"id":"si670626","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Morningbox","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Morningbox","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_178","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_178","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SaturdayCheck","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SaturdayCheck","roles":{}},{"id":"si670788","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Nightbox_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Nightbox_15","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_114","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_114","title":" Online - todos os horarios     ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_112","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_112","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_114","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_114","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_115","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_115","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_116","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_116","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_115","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_115","title":" Sabado - a partir de 8:00    ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_179","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_179","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"OnlineCheck","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"OnlineCheck","roles":{}},{"id":"si671115","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_133","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_133","title":"Quais os horários de sua preferência? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Nightbox_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Nightbox_16","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_117","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_117","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide670669","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_110","Text_Caption_111","Text_Caption_112","SmartShape_174","si670517","si670528","Afternooncheck","si670539","EspBox_175","Afternoonbox","SmartShape_176","Nightcheck","si670588","Nightbox","Select_Message_113","si670637","SmartShape_177","Morningcheck","si670626","Morningbox","SmartShape_178","SaturdayCheck","si670788","Nightbox_15","Text_Caption_114","Image_112","Image_114","Image_115","Image_116","Text_Caption_115","SmartShape_179","OnlineCheck","si671115","Text_Caption_133","Nightbox_16","Image_117"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":117},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide670669"}}},{"id":"Image_101","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_101","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_103","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_103","title":"Como você gostaria de receber o seu resultado? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_102","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_102","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_104","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_104","title":"Por Email ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_105","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_105","title":"Por Telefone ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Click_Box_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_10","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_11","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_167","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_167","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_168","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_168","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_134","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_134","title":"Obrigado por Fazer o Teste de Nível ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_7","title":"Selecione uma forma de contato ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide670058","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_101","Text_Caption_103","Image_102","Text_Caption_104","Text_Caption_105","Click_Box_10","Click_Box_11","SmartShape_167","SmartShape_168","Text_Caption_134","Failure_Shape_7"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide670058"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_106","title":" Unidade Bosque  (12) 3322-2231  Av. Andromeda, 3671 - Bosque, São José dos Campos - SP  contato-satelite@cbaidiomas.com  Unidade Jd. Esplanada  (12) 3322-0016  Av. Barão do Rio Branco, 895 - Jd. Esplanada, São José dos Campos - SP  contato-esplanada@cbaidiomas.com  Unidade Jd. das Indústrias  (12) 3204-5320  Av. Dr. João B. S. de Queiroz, 911 - Jd. das Indústrias, São José dos Campos - SP  contato-jdindustrias@cbaidiomas.com  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_171","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_171","title":"Voltar Para Website ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si670318","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Voltar Para Website ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si670330","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Voltar Para Website ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_172","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_172","title":"Ir Para Facebook ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si670344","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Ir Para Facebook ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_180","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_180","title":"Uma de nossas assistentes irá contactá-lo em ate 3 dias. Se preferir, entre em contato conosco ou visite uma de nossas unidades. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si670356","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Ir Para Facebook ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide669903","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_106","SmartShape_171","si670318","si670330","SmartShape_172","si670344","SmartShape_180","si670356"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide669903"}}},{"id":"si198158","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_7","title":"Starter: \t\t\t0-11 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_8","title":"Level A1: \t\t12-26 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_9","title":"Level A2: \t\t27-44 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_10","title":"Level B1: \t\t45-62 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_11","title":"Level B2: \t\t63-82 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_173","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_173","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si670381","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si670391","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198180","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si198224","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si198169","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Resultado ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198176","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Your Score: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198228","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continuar ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide198148","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide198148"}}},{"id":"Pool426","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":426,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Placement Test DONE","class":"project","title":"Placement Test DONE","children":["Slide5188","Slide201946","Slide203909","Slide673923","Slide674141","Slide674359","Slide674577","Slide680562","Slide681110","Slide681384","Slide681658","Slide681932","Slide682206","Slide226702","Slide686558","Slide687947","Slide688221","Slide688495","Slide688769","Slide689043","Slide689317","Slide689591","Slide689865","Slide690139","Slide690847","Slide691121","Slide691395","Slide691669","Slide691943","Slide687342","Slide686800","Slide692217","Slide692491","Slide693039","Slide693313","Slide693587","Slide693861","Slide694135","Slide694409","Slide694683","Slide694957","Slide695231","Slide695779","Slide696053","Slide696327","Slide696601","Slide696875","Slide697149","Slide697423","Slide687456","Slide686984","Slide697697","Slide697971","Slide698462","Slide698736","Slide699010","Slide699558","Slide699832","Slide700106","Slide700380","Slide700654","Slide700928","Slide701202","Slide701476","Slide701750","Slide702024","Slide702789","Slide703063","Slide703337","Slide687570","Slide687184","Slide703611","Slide703885","Slide704159","Slide704433","Slide704707","Slide704981","Slide705255","Slide705529","Slide705803","Slide706625","Slide706899","Slide707173","Slide707447","Slide707721","Slide707995","Slide708269","Slide708543","Slide708817","Slide709091","Slide709365","Slide687684","Slide547673","Slide646629","Slide670669","Slide670058","Slide669903","Slide198148"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":382,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":false,"questions":["Slide203909q0","Slide673923q1","Slide674141q2","Slide674359q3","Slide674577q4","Slide680562q5","Slide681110q6","Slide681384q7","Slide681658q8","Slide681932q9","Slide682206q10","Slide687947q11","Slide688221q12","Slide688495q13","Slide688769q14","Slide689043q15","Slide689317q16","Slide689591q17","Slide689865q18","Slide690139q19","Slide690847q20","Slide691121q21","Slide691395q22","Slide691669q23","Slide691943q24","Slide692217q25","Slide692491q26","Slide693039q27","Slide693313q28","Slide693587q29","Slide693861q30","Slide694135q31","Slide694409q32","Slide694683q33","Slide694957q34","Slide695231q35","Slide695779q36","Slide696053q37","Slide696327q38","Slide696601q39","Slide696875q40","Slide697149q41","Slide697423q42","Slide697697q43","Slide697971q44","Slide698462q45","Slide698736q46","Slide699010q47","Slide699558q48","Slide699832q49","Slide700106q50","Slide700380q51","Slide700654q52","Slide700928q53","Slide701202q54","Slide701476q55","Slide701750q56","Slide702024q57","Slide702789q58","Slide703063q59","Slide703337q60","Slide703611q61","Slide703885q62","Slide704159q63","Slide704433q64","Slide704707q65","Slide704981q66","Slide705255q67","Slide705529q68","Slide705803q69","Slide706625q70","Slide706899q71","Slide707173q72","Slide707447q73","Slide707721q74","Slide707995q75","Slide708269q76","Slide708543q77","Slide708817q78","Slide709091q79","Slide709365q80"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":81,"passScore":49}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"launch_content","SCCriteria":"launch_content","exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide5188","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide201946","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide203909","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide673923","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide674141","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide674359","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide674577","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide680562","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide681110","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide681384","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide681658","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide681932","title":"Slide 12"},{"id":"Slide682206","title":"Slide 13"},{"id":"Slide226702","title":"Slide 14"},{"id":"Slide686558","title":"Slide 15"},{"id":"Slide687947","title":"Slide 16"},{"id":"Slide688221","title":"Slide 17"},{"id":"Slide688495","title":"Slide 18"},{"id":"Slide688769","title":"Slide 19"},{"id":"Slide689043","title":"Slide 20"},{"id":"Slide689317","title":"Slide 21"},{"id":"Slide689591","title":"Slide 22"},{"id":"Slide689865","title":"Slide 23"},{"id":"Slide690139","title":"Slide 24"},{"id":"Slide690847","title":"Slide 25"},{"id":"Slide691121","title":"Slide 26"},{"id":"Slide691395","title":"Slide 27"},{"id":"Slide691669","title":"Slide 28"},{"id":"Slide691943","title":"Slide 29"},{"id":"Slide687342","title":"Slide 30"},{"id":"Slide686800","title":"Slide 31"},{"id":"Slide692217","title":"Slide 32"},{"id":"Slide692491","title":"Slide 33"},{"id":"Slide693039","title":"Slide 34"},{"id":"Slide693313","title":"Slide 35"},{"id":"Slide693587","title":"Slide 36"},{"id":"Slide693861","title":"Slide 37"},{"id":"Slide694135","title":"Slide 38"},{"id":"Slide694409","title":"Slide 39"},{"id":"Slide694683","title":"Slide 40"},{"id":"Slide694957","title":"Slide 41"},{"id":"Slide695231","title":"Slide 42"},{"id":"Slide695779","title":"Slide 43"},{"id":"Slide696053","title":"Slide 44"},{"id":"Slide696327","title":"Slide 45"},{"id":"Slide696601","title":"Slide 46"},{"id":"Slide696875","title":"Slide 47"},{"id":"Slide697149","title":"Slide 48"},{"id":"Slide697423","title":"Slide 49"},{"id":"Slide687456","title":"Slide 50"},{"id":"Slide686984","title":"Slide 51"},{"id":"Slide697697","title":"Slide 52"},{"id":"Slide697971","title":"Slide 53"},{"id":"Slide698462","title":"Slide 54"},{"id":"Slide698736","title":"Slide 55"},{"id":"Slide699010","title":"Slide 56"},{"id":"Slide699558","title":"Slide 57"},{"id":"Slide699832","title":"Slide 58"},{"id":"Slide700106","title":"Slide 59"},{"id":"Slide700380","title":"Slide 60"},{"id":"Slide700654","title":"Slide 61"},{"id":"Slide700928","title":"Slide 62"},{"id":"Slide701202","title":"Slide 63"},{"id":"Slide701476","title":"Slide 64"},{"id":"Slide701750","title":"Slide 65"},{"id":"Slide702024","title":"Slide 66"},{"id":"Slide702789","title":"Slide 67"},{"id":"Slide703063","title":"Slide 68"},{"id":"Slide703337","title":"Slide 69"},{"id":"Slide687570","title":"Slide 70"},{"id":"Slide687184","title":"Slide 71"},{"id":"Slide703611","title":"Slide 72"},{"id":"Slide703885","title":"Slide 73"},{"id":"Slide704159","title":"Slide 74"},{"id":"Slide704433","title":"Slide 75"},{"id":"Slide704707","title":"Slide 76"},{"id":"Slide704981","title":"Slide 77"},{"id":"Slide705255","title":"Slide 78"},{"id":"Slide705529","title":"Slide 79"},{"id":"Slide705803","title":"Slide 80"},{"id":"Slide706625","title":"Slide 81"},{"id":"Slide706899","title":"Slide 82"},{"id":"Slide707173","title":"Slide 83"},{"id":"Slide707447","title":"Slide 84"},{"id":"Slide707721","title":"Slide 85"},{"id":"Slide707995","title":"Slide 86"},{"id":"Slide708269","title":"Slide 87"},{"id":"Slide708543","title":"Slide 88"},{"id":"Slide708817","title":"Slide 89"},{"id":"Slide709091","title":"Slide 90"},{"id":"Slide709365","title":"Slide 91"},{"id":"Slide687684","title":"Slide 92"},{"id":"Slide547673","title":"Slide 93"},{"id":"Slide646629","title":"Slide 94"},{"id":"Slide670669","title":"Slide 95"},{"id":"Slide670058","title":"Slide 96"},{"id":"Slide669903","title":"Slide 97"},{"id":"Slide198148","title":"Slide 98"}]}